<?xml version='1.0'?>
<!--
<!DOCTYPE book PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.1.2//EN"
                      "http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.1.2/docbookx.dtd">
-->                      
<chapter>
	<title>2004-03-23 Human expressive language is repressive of heavenly realm</title>
	<para>
		On the morning of 2004-03-23 I dreamt of a classroom setting.
		The students in the class including Bimbo and myself were assigned laboratory experiments that included
		programming tasks. The instructor advised against wasting efforts on creative programming.
		The template examples accompany the course should guide our endevors. 
 
		This will offer the opportunity to prepare on presenting the highlights in an interactive acting scenario.
		
		The Bimbo in the dream, is not clearly identified.
		But, I can only recall two Bimbo class mates. One Bimbo, the first, is a class mate at
		Staff School, University of Ile Ife, Nigeria, a she. The second Bimbo, is a male, and his
		lastname is Oshiyemi. This second Bimbo, and I, were class mates at Baptist Academy, Lagos, Nigeria.

		I do not remember the last name of the first Bimbo, and even the last name, I recall might be a nee.
		But when the spirit sees that we are lacking in knowledge, it makes up, for us.
		So what the spirit can not impart by saying the fullname, it compensates by identifying the
		person, in our conscience. Also, the Bimbo in the dream, is not relevant to the discussion.
		
		I lean towards the first Bimbo, from an earthly perspective, following the law of first
		introduction, as mentioned by Chuck Missler, Koinonia House, KHouse.org.
		
		The name, Bimbo, I believe, is an abbreviation, for Abimbola, which is Adegoke Benitoluwa Adeniji's
		other name. Abimbola is a Yoruba name, meaning, I was born as wealth.

		There is an arrangement to live a life, worthy of Him, in outer living.
		The practicality of the bible, in our foundation stance.
	</para>

	<sect1>
		<title>2007-09-04T01:31:00 Nlt : Nlf. Life time : Life frame. Years lived : Number of children</title>
		<example>
			There are 3.5 biblical years between 2004-03-23 and 2007-09-04.
			I did not completely hear the story of this dream, I can attest to the fact that God's blessing
			is reflected in the length of years that we live, and the number of children that we have.
			Our length of years, also encompass how long we influence our world,
			even when we are physically dead.
			Included among our children, are our spiritual offspring, that we spiritually impact
			(Exodus 20:12, Deuteronomy 5:16).	
		</example>
	</sect1>

	<sect1>
		<title>2007-10-28 Adeyemo Adewuyi Adeniji. Adegoke Abimbola Adeniji.</title>
		<example>
			There are 1313 days between 2004-03-23 and 2007-10-28.
			I have combined the names of a father and son.
		</example>
	</sect1>
	
<!--
<sect1><title>First Section</title>
<para> ... </para>
<example> ... </example>
</sect1>
-->
</chapter>