<?xml version='1.0'?>
<!--
<!DOCTYPE book PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.1.2//EN"
                      "http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.1.2/docbookx.dtd">
-->                      
<chapter>
 <title>Abstract</title>
<para>
</para>

<sect1>
 <title>Aims</title>
<para>
 This thesis aims to experience life in the exterior.
 It will accumulate incidences of prophetic occurence in our transistion towards spiritual worthwhile.
 Historical events and significant daily living will match our goal.
</para>
</sect1>

<sect1>
 <title>Materials &amp; Methods</title>
<para>
 Segregated living offers opportunity for excluding earthly interference and intervention from divine inference.
 The subject's infrastructure will practice and mediate God's conclusion.
</para>
</sect1>

<sect1>
 <title>Results</title>
<para>
 Each religion's devotion and obedience formulate duplicity and pairing up.
 The best results conceive invitee and invitation, transversal.
 We see a correlation and distance between how I want to been seen, and how I am seen.
 Our thought and action in our interpretation of the Word precede the eternal after effects, reception, and realization.
 Noriko Yoshida, cumulatively yields prognosis, treatment for the disease.
 The chance meeting, correspondence, affection, kin.
</para>
</sect1>

<sect1>
 <title>Conclusions</title>
<para>
 The subject's re-location to Australia followed three years of hiatus in his country of birth, Nigeria, domicile republic.
 Australia's special skills, residency, citizenship, olympic entree, transplanting marriage, facilitates colleagues' medallion.
 The door opens ajar, in climax penalizing delusion and distortion; fine-tuning predate, precursor, and knit.
</para>
</sect1>

<sect1>
 <title>Keywords</title>
<para>
 WordEngineering, Ocean Senior
</para>
</sect1>

<sect1>
 <title>Quote</title>
<para>
 The pauper's song, I 've kept myself lean to lent; the architecture is the art's anatomy.
 I used to ask when does dormancy obey durancy.
 I think their is a lacking in you, and this is a stimulus to fulfill that gap.
 We are our own step, step.
 Accused for playing basketball, off loading, welling with neighbors as he marched towards his parental reunion after twelve years; condemned for sharing the fruit foliage with his adopted at passover's passion.
 Suzerainty Treaties. Covenant.
</para>
</sect1>

<!--
<sect1><title>First Section</title>
<para> ... </para>
<example> ... </example>
</sect1>
-->
</chapter>