<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type='text/xsl' href='TheWord.xslt'?>
<wordOfGod>
 <TheWord>
  <SequenceOrderId>5</SequenceOrderId>
  <Dated>2003-07-26T00:00:00.0000000-08:00</Dated>
  <ScriptureReference>Ruth 3:18, Ruth 4:1-2, 1 Samuel 9:22, 1 Samuel 16:11, 1 Kings 1:13, 1 Kings 1:17, 1 Kings 1:20, 1 Kings 1:24, 1 Kings 1:27, 1 Kings 1:30, 1 Kings 1:35, 1 Kings 1:48, 1 Kings 3:6, 1 Kings 8:25, 2 Chronicles 6:16, Psalms 26:5, Psalms 69:12, Psalms 132:12, Ecclesiastes 10:6, Isaiah 14:13, Isaiah 16:5, Isaiah 42:7, Jeremiah 13:13, Jeremiah 13:18, Ezekiel 26:16, Ezekiel 28:2, Ezekiel 33:31, Ezekiel 44:3, Joel 3:12, Luke 1:79, Luke 14:8, Luke 14:10, Revelation 3:21</ScriptureReference>
  <ScriptureReferenceURI>http://bible.crosswalk.com/OnlineStudyBible/bible.cgi?new=1&amp;word=Ruth+3%3A18%2C+Ruth+4%3A1-2%2C+1+Samuel+9%3A22%2C+1+Samuel+16%3A11%2C+1+Kings+1%3A13%2C+1+Kings+1%3A17%2C+1+Kings+1%3A20%2C+1+Kings+1%3A24%2C+1+Kings+1%3A27%2C+1+Kings+1%3A30%2C+1+Kings+1%3A35%2C+1+Kings+1%3A48%2C+1+Kings+3%3A6%2C+1+Kings+8%3A25%2C+2+Chronicles+6%3A16%2C+Psalms+26%3A5%2C+Psalms+69%3A12%2C+Psalms+132%3A12%2C+Ecclesiastes+10%3A6%2C+Isaiah+14%3A13%2C+Isaiah+16%3A5%2C+Isaiah+42%3A7%2C+Jeremiah+13%3A13%2C+Jeremiah+13%3A18%2C+Ezekiel+26%3A16%2C+Ezekiel+28%3A2%2C+Ezekiel+33%3A31%2C+Ezekiel+44%3A3%2C+Joel+3%3A12%2C+Luke+1%3A79%2C+Luke+14%3A8%2C+Luke+14%3A10%2C+Revelation+3%3A21&amp;section=0&amp;version=nkj&amp;language=en</ScriptureReferenceURI>
  <Title>Joko e ni ile.</Title>
  <Keyword />
  <Remember>
   <SequenceOrderId>314</SequenceOrderId>
   <DatedFrom>2003-07-09T00:00:00.0000000-08:00</DatedFrom>
   <DatedUntil>2003-07-27T00:00:00.0000000-08:00</DatedUntil>
   <SignIndex>18</SignIndex>
   <Commentary>Kokuho Rice U.S. #1 Extra Fancy New Crop Net Wt. 20LBS 9.07kg.</Commentary>
   <Filename>Comforter_-_20030709BeContentWithYourWages_NothingButTheBloodOfJesus_AsILookThroughLifeIWillTakeYouWithMe_KuroLogbaE.xml</Filename>
   <ScriptureReference>Genesis 29:15, Genesis 30:28, Genesis 31:7, Genesis 31:8, Genesis 31:41, Exodus 2:9, Leviticus 19:13, Jeremiah 22:13, Ezekiel 29:18, Ezekiel 29:19, Haggai 1:6, Malachi 3:5, Luke 3:14, John 4:36, Romans 6:23, 2 Corinthians 11:8, 2 Peter 2:15</ScriptureReference>
   <ScriptureReferenceURI>http://bible.crosswalk.com/OnlineStudyBible/bible.cgi?new=1&amp;word=Genesis+29%3A15%2C+Genesis+30%3A28%2C+Genesis+31%3A7%2C+Genesis+31%3A8%2C+Genesis+31%3A41%2C+Exodus+2%3A9%2C+Leviticus+19%3A13%2C+Jeremiah+22%3A13%2C+Ezekiel+29%3A18%2C+Ezekiel+29%3A19%2C+Haggai+1%3A6%2C+Malachi+3%3A5%2C+Luke+3%3A14%2C+John+4%3A36%2C+Romans+6%3A23%2C+2+Corinthians+11%3A8%2C+2+Peter+2%3A15&amp;section=0&amp;version=nkj&amp;language=en</ScriptureReferenceURI>
  </Remember>
  <ScriptureReading>
   <SequenceOrderId>61</SequenceOrderId>
   <ScriptureReference>Isaiah 1-24, Isaiah 33-48, Daniel 1-4</ScriptureReference>
   <ScriptureReferenceURI>http://bible.crosswalk.com/OnlineStudyBible/bible.cgi?new=1&amp;word=Isaiah+1-24%2C+Isaiah+33-48%2C+Daniel+1-4&amp;section=0&amp;version=nkj&amp;language=en</ScriptureReferenceURI>
  </ScriptureReading>
  <ScriptureReading>
   <SequenceOrderId>62</SequenceOrderId>
   <ScriptureReference>Daniel 5-12, Hosea 1-14, Joel 1-3, Amos 1-4</ScriptureReference>
   <ScriptureReferenceURI>http://bible.crosswalk.com/OnlineStudyBible/bible.cgi?new=1&amp;word=Daniel+5-12%2C+Hosea+1-14%2C+Joel+1-3%2C+Amos+1-4&amp;section=0&amp;version=nkj&amp;language=en</ScriptureReferenceURI>
  </ScriptureReading>
  <!--
  <Sign>
   <SequenceOrderId>19</SequenceOrderId>
   <Measure />
   <SignIndex />
   <Commentary />
   <ScriptureReference />
   <ScriptureReferenceURI />
  </Sign>
  -->
  <BibleWord>
   <SequenceOrderId>178</SequenceOrderId>
   <Word>Sit</Word>
   <Commentary>
Then said Naomi, Sit still, Ruth, my daughter, until you know how the matter will fall: for Boaz will not be in rest, until he has finished the thing this day (Ruth 3:18).
Then went Boaz up to the gate, and he sat down there: and, behold, the nearer kinsman of whom Boaz spoke came by; unto whom he said, Ho, such a one! turn aside, sit down here. And the nearer kinsman turned aside, and sat down.
Boaz took ten men of the elders of the city, and said, Sit you down here. And they sat down (Ruth 4:1-2).

Samuel took Saul and his servant, and brought them into the parlor, and made them sit in the chiefest place among them that were bidden, which were about thirty persons (1 Samuel 9:22).

Samuel said unto Jesse, Are here all thy children? And he said, There remains yet the youngest, and, behold, he keeps the sheep. And Samuel said unto Jesse, Send and fetch him: for we will not sit down till he come hither (1 Samuel 16:11).

Nathan the prophet said to Bathsheba the mother of Solomon, Go and get unto king David, and say unto him, Did not you, my lord, O king, swear unto your handmaid, saying, Assuredly Solomon thy son shall reign after me, and he shall sit upon my throne? why then does Adonijah reign? (1 Kings 1:13).
Bathsheba said unto king Solomon, My lord, you sware by the LORD your God unto your handmaid, saying, Assuredly Solomon your son shall reign after me, and he shall sit upon my throne (1 Kings 1:17).
And you, my lord, O king, the eyes of all Israel are upon you, that you should tell them who shall sit on the throne of my lord the king after him (1 Kings 1:20).
And Nathan said, My lord, O king, have you said, Adonijah shall reign after me, and he shall sit upon my throne? (1 Kings 1:24).
Is this thing done by my lord the king, and you have not showed it unto your servant, who should sit on the throne of my lord the king after him? (1 Kings 1:27).
Even as I sware unto Bathsheba by the LORD God of Israel, saying, Assuredly Solomon your son shall reign after me, and he shall sit upon my throne in my stead; even so will I certainly do this day (1 Kings 1:30).
Then Zadok the priest, and Nathan the prophet, and Benaiah the son of Jehoiada, shall come up after Solomon, that he may come and sit upon my throne; for he shall be king in my stead: and I have appointed him to be ruler over Israel and over Judah (1 Kings 1:35).
Jonathan the son of Abiathar the priest said, king David said, Blessed be the LORD God of Israel, which has given one to sit on my throne this day, mine eyes even seeing it (1 Kings 1:48).

Solomon said, You have showed unto your servant David my father great mercy, according as he walked before you in truth, and in righteousness, and in uprightness of heart with You; and You have kept for him this great kindness, that You have given him a son to sit on his throne, as it is this day (1 Kings 3:6).

Therefore now, LORD God of Israel, keep with your servant David my father that You promised him, saying, There shall not fail you a man in My sight to sit on the throne of Israel; so that your children take heed to their way, that they walk before me as you have walked before me (1 Kings 8:25).

Now therefore, O LORD God of Israel, keep with Your servant David my father that which You have promised him, saying, There shall not fail you a man in My sight to sit upon the throne of Israel; yet so that your children take heed to their way to walk in my law, as you have walked before Me (2 Chronicles 6:16).

I have hated the congregation of evil doers; and will not sit with the wicked (Psalms 26:5).

They that sit in the gate speak against me; and I was the song of the drunkards (Psalms 69:12).

If your children will keep My covenant and My testimony that I shall teach them, their children shall also sit upon your throne for evermore (Psalms 132:12).

Folly is set in great dignity, and the rich sit in low place (Ecclesiastes 10:6).

For you have said in your heart, I will ascend into heaven, I will exalt my throne above the stars of God: I will sit also upon the mount of the congregation, in the sides of the north (Isaiah 14:13).

In mercy shall the throne be established: and he shall sit upon it in truth in the tabernacle of David, judging, and seeking judgment, and hasting righteousness (Isaiah 16:5).

To open the blind eyes, to bring out the prisoners from the prison, and them that sit in darkness out of the prison house (Isaiah 42:7).

Then shall you say unto them, This said the LORD, Behold, I will fill all the inhabitants of this land, even the kings that sit upon the throne, and the priests, and the prophets, and all the inhabitants, with drunkenness (Jeremiah 13:13).

Say unto the king and to the queen, Humble yourselves, sit down: for your principalities shall come down, even the crown of your glory (Jeremiah 13:18).

Then all the princes of the sea shall come down from their thrones, and lay away their robes, and put off their broidered garments: they shall clothe themselves with trembling; they shall sit upon the ground, and shall tremble at every moment, and be astonished at you (Ezekiel 26:16).

Son of man, say unto the prince of Tyrus, This said the Lord GOD; Because your heart is lifted up, and you have said, I am a God, I sit in the seat of God, in the midst of the seas; yet you are a man, and not God, though you set your heart as the heart of God (Ezekiel 28:2).

They come unto you as the people come, and they sit before you as My people, and they hear your words, but they will not do them: for with their mouth they show much love, but their heart goes after their covetousness (Ezekiel 33:31).

The gate of the outward sanctuary which looks toward the east is for the prince; the prince, he shall sit in it to eat bread before the LORD; he shall enter by the way of the porch of that gate, and shall go out by the way of the same (Ezekiel 44:3).

Let the heathen be wakened, and come up to the valley of Jehoshaphat: for there will I sit to judge all the heathen round about (Joel 3:12).

To give light to them that sit in darkness and in the shadow of death, to guide our feet into the way of peace (Luke 1:79).

When you are bidden of any man to a wedding, sit not down in the highest room; less a more honourable man than you be bidden of him (Luke 14:8).

But when you are bidden, go and sit down in the lowest room; that when he that bade you comes, he may say unto you, Friend, go up higher: then shall you have worship in the presence of them that sit at meat with you (Luke 14:10).

To him that overcomes will I grant to sit with me in My throne, even as I also overcame, and am set down with My Father in His throne (Revelation 3:21).

   </Commentary>
  </BibleWord>

  <AlphabetSequence>
   <SequenceOrderId>452</SequenceOrderId>
   <Word>Joko e ni ile.</Word>
   <AlphabetSequenceIndex>105</AlphabetSequenceIndex>
   <ScriptureReference>Genesis 4:25, Leviticus 15, 2 Corinthians 7, Revelation 18:4</ScriptureReference>
   <ScriptureReferenceURI>http://bible.crosswalk.com/OnlineStudyBible/bible.cgi?new=1&amp;word=Genesis+4%3A25%2C+Leviticus+15%2C+2+Corinthians+7%2C+Revelation+18%3A4&amp;section=0&amp;version=nkj&amp;language=en</ScriptureReferenceURI>  
  </AlphabetSequence>

  <CaseBasedReasoning>
   <SequenceOrderId>1024</SequenceOrderId>
   <Commentary>
    (And she said) Bathsheba (sneeze) said unto king Solomon, My lord, you sware by the LORD your God unto your handmaid, saying, Assuredly Solomon your son shall reign after me, and he shall sit upon my throne (1 Kings 1:17). Naked. Kokuho Rice U.S. #1 Extra Fancy New Crop Net Wt. 20LBS 9.07kg. Maria Berta Classic Biscuits / Galletas Clasicas Original Maria Cookies from Spain Net Weight / Peso Neto: 7 oz (200g) Product of Spain / Producto De Espana Manufactured By/Fabricado Por: Grupo Siro CTRA Burgos-Portugal, KM. 84 34200 Venta De Banos (Palencia) Spain. ISBN: 0 85644 00099 9.
   </Commentary>    
   <ScriptureReference>1 Kings 1:17</ScriptureReference>
   <ScriptureReferenceURI>http://bible.crosswalk.com/OnlineStudyBible/bible.cgi?new=1&amp;word=1+Kings+1%3A17&amp;section=0&amp;version=nkj&amp;language=en</ScriptureReferenceURI>  
  </CaseBasedReasoning>

  <CaseBasedReasoning>
   <SequenceOrderId>1025</SequenceOrderId>
   <Dated>2003-07-27T00:00:00.0000000-08:00</Dated>
   <Commentary>Naked. Wake-up Orientation: Feets at the center of the horizontal couch and at the beginning of the vertical couch; head at the 66.67% of the vertical couch. Kokuho Rice U.S. #1 Extra Fancy New Crop Net Wt. 20LBS 9.07kg.</Commentary>
  </CaseBasedReasoning>

  <!--
  <Export>
   <SequenceOrderId>23</SequenceOrderId>
   <Dated />
   <Commentary />
  </Export>
  -->

  <Software>
   <SequenceOrderId>232</SequenceOrderId>
   <Commentary>UtilityDatabaseRelease20030726.cs WordEngineeringRelease20030726.config</Commentary>
  </Software>
  
  <ClassAssociates>
   <SequenceOrderId>250</SequenceOrderId>
   <Commentary>Scripture Reading: Noise, cry. CaseBasedReasoning 1025: Monitor noise.</Commentary>
   <ScriptureReference>Isaiah 1-24, Isaiah 33-48, Daniel 1-4</ScriptureReference>
   <ScriptureReferenceURI>http://bible.crosswalk.com/OnlineStudyBible/bible.cgi?new=1&amp;word=Isaiah+1-24%2C+Isaiah+33-48%2C+Daniel+1-4&amp;section=0&amp;version=nkj&amp;language=en</ScriptureReferenceURI>
  </ClassAssociates>

  <ClassAssociates>
   <SequenceOrderId>251</SequenceOrderId>
   <Dated>2003-07-27T18:00:00.0000000-08:00</Dated>
   <Commentary>Scripture Reading: Noise. Computer: on, cry, loud.</Commentary>
  </ClassAssociates>
  
  </TheWord>
</wordOfGod>