<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type='text/xsl' href='TheWord.xslt'?>
<wordOfGod>
 <TheWord>

  <SequenceOrderId>36</SequenceOrderId>
  <Dated>2003-08-12T00:00:00.0000000-08:00</Dated>
  <ScriptureReference>Genesis 12:4, Genesis 12:5, Exodus 2:8, Judges 14:16, 1 Samuel 15:33, 1 Kings 3:27, 1 Kings 17:23, Psalms 131:2, Proverbs 29:15, Isaiah 8:4, Matthew 2:11, Matthew 2:13, Matthew 2:14, Matthew 2:20, Matthew 2:21, Luke 2:43</ScriptureReference>
  <ScriptureReferenceURI>http://bible.crosswalk.com/OnlineStudyBible/bible.cgi?new=1&amp;word=Genesis+12%3A4%2C+Genesis+12%3A5%2C+Exodus+2%3A8%2C+Judges+14%3A16%2C+1+Samuel+15%3A33%2C+1+Kings+3%3A27%2C+1+Kings+17%3A23%2C+Psalms+131%3A2%2C+Proverbs+29%3A15%2C+Isaiah+8%3A4%2C+Matthew+2%3A11%2C+Matthew+2%3A13%2C+Matthew+2%3A14%2C+Matthew+2%3A20%2C+Matthew+2%3A21%2C+Luke+2%3A43&amp;section=0&amp;version=nkj&amp;language=en</ScriptureReferenceURI>  
  <Title>A child and His mother.</Title>
  <Commentary />
  <Keyword />

  <!--
  <Prophet>
   <SequenceOrderId>23</SequenceOrderId>
   <Commentary></Commentary>
  </Prophet>
  -->

  <Remember>
   <SequenceOrderId>337</SequenceOrderId>
   <DatedFrom>2003-04-29T00:00:00.0000000-08:00</DatedFrom>
   <DatedUntil>2003-08-12T00:00:00.0000000-08:00</DatedUntil>
   <SignIndex>105</SignIndex>
   <Commentary>Floppy disk TDK MF-2HD IBM/DOS Formatted. C1E25D1D1J1.</Commentary>
   <Filename>Comforter_-_200304290601WeShouldContinueToStriveForTheUnitedStatesShouldWeHesitate.xml</Filename>
   <ScriptureReference>Joshua 15:5, Joshua 16:6, Joshua 17:10, Judges 21:19, 1 Chronicles 26:14, 1 Chronicles 26:17, Ezekiel 40:19, Ezekiel 40:23, Ezekiel 40:44, Ezekiel 47:2, Daniel 11:44, Joel 2:20, Amos 8:12</ScriptureReference>
   <ScriptureReferenceURI>http://bible.crosswalk.com/OnlineStudyBible/bible.cgi?new=1&amp;word=Joshua+15%3A5%2C+Joshua+16%3A6%2C+Joshua+17%3A10%2C+Judges+21%3A19%2C+1+Chronicles+26%3A14%2C+1+Chronicles+26%3A17%2C+Ezekiel+40%3A19%2C+Ezekiel+40%3A23%2C+Ezekiel+40%3A44%2C+Ezekiel+47%3A2%2C+Daniel+11%3A44%2C+Joel+2%3A20%2C+Amos+8%3A12&amp;section=0&amp;version=nkj&amp;language=en</ScriptureReferenceURI>
  </Remember>

  <Remember>
   <SequenceOrderId>338</SequenceOrderId>
   <DatedFrom>2003-05-17T00:00:00.0000000-08:00</DatedFrom>
   <DatedUntil>2003-08-12T00:00:00.0000000-08:00</DatedUntil>
   <SignIndex>87</SignIndex>
   <Commentary>Yuri Japanese Restaurant. 3810 Mowry Avenue, Fremont CA 94538. Tel: (510) 945-6701.</Commentary>
   <Filename>Comforter_-_20030517JehovahRopheOfeRiDa_YourHeadInTheTopInTheNineteenEightiesOrYourSmallerVesselsInTheTop.xml</Filename>
   <ScriptureReference>Exodus 2:2, Hebrews 11:23-29</ScriptureReference>
   <ScriptureReferenceURI>http://bible.crosswalk.com/OnlineStudyBible/bible.cgi?new=1&amp;word=Exodus+2%3A2%2C+Hebrews+11%3A23-29&amp;section=0&amp;version=nkj&amp;language=en</ScriptureReferenceURI>
  </Remember>

  <Remember>
   <SequenceOrderId>339</SequenceOrderId>
   <DatedFrom>2003-08-04T00:00:00.0000000-08:00</DatedFrom>
   <DatedUntil>2003-08-12T00:00:00.0000000-08:00</DatedUntil>
   <SignIndex>8</SignIndex>
   <Commentary>Highway 84 Stevenson Blvd Exit: Full sun towards the right; half moon towards the left curved towards the right.</Commentary>
   <Filename>Comforter_-_20030804IStillBelieveAndIAmEntrustedToYou_TurningBack_LearningToParticipate.xml</Filename>
   <ScriptureReference>Matthew 2:9, Matthew 2:12-13, Matthew 10:14, Mark 5:20, Mark 9:40, Luke 1:23, Luke 2:29, Luke 2:37, Luke 5:10, Luke 5:25, Luke 9:4, Luke 9:6, Luke 10:35, Luke 10:42, Luke 11:36, Luke 21:21, Luke 24:12, John 5:15</ScriptureReference>
   <ScriptureReferenceURI>http://bible.crosswalk.com/OnlineStudyBible/bible.cgi?new=1&amp;word=Matthew+2%3A9%2C+Matthew+2%3A12-13%2C+Matthew+10%3A14%2C+Mark+5%3A20%2C+Mark+9%3A40%2C+Luke+1%3A23%2C+Luke+2%3A29%2C+Luke+2%3A37%2C+Luke+5%3A10%2C+Luke+5%3A25%2C+Luke+9%3A4%2C+Luke+9%3A6%2C+Luke+10%3A35%2C+Luke+10%3A42%2C+Luke+11%3A36%2C+Luke+21%3A21%2C+Luke+24%3A12%2C+John+5%3A15&amp;section=0&amp;version=nkj&amp;language=en</ScriptureReferenceURI>  
  </Remember>

  <!--
  <ScriptureReading>
   <SequenceOrderId>65</SequenceOrderId>
   <ScriptureReference></ScriptureReference>
   <ScriptureReferenceURI></ScriptureReferenceURI>
  </ScriptureReading>
  -->

  <Sign>
   <SequenceOrderId>23</SequenceOrderId>
   <Measure>Week</Measure>
   <SignIndex>3.5</SignIndex>
   <Commentary>He shall confirm a covenant with many for one week; but in the middle of the week he shall bring an end to sacrifice and offering. And on the wings of abominations shall be one who makes desolate, even until the consummation, which is determined, is poured on the desolate (Daniel 9:27).</Commentary>
   <ScriptureReference>Daniel 9:27</ScriptureReference>
   <ScriptureReferenceURI>http://bible.crosswalk.com/OnlineStudyBible/bible.cgi?new=1&amp;word=Daniel+9%3A27&amp;section=0&amp;version=nkj&amp;language=en</ScriptureReferenceURI>
  </Sign>

  <Sign>
   <SequenceOrderId>24</SequenceOrderId>
   <Measure>Day</Measure>
   <SignIndex>8</SignIndex>
   <Commentary>
    He that is eight days old shall be circumcised among you, every man child in your generations, he that is born in the house, or bought with money of any stranger, which is not of your seed (Genesis 17:12).
    Abraham circumcised his son Isaac being eight days old, as God had commanded him (Genesis 21:4).
    In the eighth day the flesh of his foreskin shall be circumcised (Leviticus 12:3).
    He shall bring them on the eighth day for his cleansing unto the priest, unto the door of the tabernacle of the congregation, before the LORD (Leviticus 14:23).
    On the eighth day he shall take to him two turtledoves, or two young pigeons, and come before the LORD unto the door of the tabernacle of the congregation, and give them unto the priest (Leviticus 15:14).
    On the eighth day she shall take unto her two turtles, or two young pigeons, and bring them unto the priest, to the door of the tabernacle of the congregation ((Leviticus 15:29).
    On the eighth day he shall bring two turtles, or two young pigeons, to the priest, to the door of the tabernacle of the congregation (Numbers 6:10).
    On the eighth day he sent the people away: and they blessed the king, and went unto their tents joyful and glad of heart for all the goodness that the LORD had done for David his servant, and for His people (1 Kings 8:66).
    When eight days were accomplished for the circumcising of the child, his name was called JESUS, which was so named of the angel before he was conceived in the womb (Luke 2:21).
    God gave him the covenant of circumcision: and so Abraham begat Isaac, and circumcised him the eighth day; and Isaac begat Jacob; and Jacob begat the twelve patriarchs (Acts 7:8).
    Circumcised the eighth day, of the stock of Israel, of the tribe of Benjamin, an Hebrew of the Hebrews; as touching the law, a Pharisee (Philippians 3:5).
   </Commentary>
   <ScriptureReference>Genesis 17:12, Genesis 21:4, Exodus 22:30, Leviticus 9:1, Leviticus 12:3, Leviticus 14:10, Leviticus 14:23, Leviticus 15:14, Leviticus 15:29, Leviticus 22:27, Leviticus 23:36, Leviticus 23:39, Numbers 6:10, Numbers 7:54, Numbers 29:35, 1 Kings 8:66, 2 Chronicles 7:9, 2 Chronicles 29:17, Nehemiah 8:18, Ezekiel 43:27, Luke 1:59, Luke 2:21, Luke 9:28, John 20:26, Acts 7:8, Philippians 3:5</ScriptureReference>
   <ScriptureReferenceURI>http://bible.crosswalk.com/OnlineStudyBible/bible.cgi?new=1&amp;word=Genesis+17%3A12%2C+Genesis+21%3A4%2C+Exodus+22%3A30%2C+Leviticus+9%3A1%2C+Leviticus+12%3A3%2C+Leviticus+14%3A10%2C+Leviticus+14%3A23%2C+Leviticus+15%3A14%2C+Leviticus+15%3A29%2C+Leviticus+22%3A27%2C+Leviticus+23%3A36%2C+Leviticus+23%3A39%2C+Numbers+6%3A10%2C+Numbers+7%3A54%2C+Numbers+29%3A35%2C+1+Kings+8%3A66%2C+2+Chronicles+7%3A9%2C+2+Chronicles+29%3A17%2C+Nehemiah+8%3A18%2C+Ezekiel+43%3A27%2C+Luke+1%3A59%2C+Luke+2%3A21%2C+Luke+9%3A28%2C+John+20%3A26%2C+Acts+7%3A8%2C+Philippians+3%3A5&amp;section=0&amp;version=nkj&amp;language=en</ScriptureReferenceURI>
  </Sign>
 
  <BibleWord>
   <SequenceOrderId>212</SequenceOrderId>
   <Word>Child ... Mother</Word>
   <Commentary>
So Abram departed, as the LORD had spoken unto him; and Lot went with him: and Abram was seventy and five years old when he departed out of Haran (Genesis 12:4).
Abram took Sarai his wife, and Lot his brother's son, and all their substance that they had gathered, and the souls that they had gotten in Haran; and they went forth to go into the land of Canaan; and into the land of Canaan they came (Genesis 12:5).
Pharaoh's daughter said to her, Go. And the maid went and called the child's mother (Exodus 2:8).
Samson's wife wept before him, and said, You do but hate me, and love me not: you have put forth a riddle unto the children of my people, and have not told it me. And he said unto her, Behold, I have not told it my father nor my mother, and shall I tell it you? (Judges 14:16).
Samuel said, As the sword has made women childless, so shall your mother be childless among women. And Samuel hewed Agag in pieces before the LORD in Gilgal (1 Samuel 15:33).
The king answered and said, Give her the living child, and in no wise slay it: she is the mother thereof (1 Kings 3:27).
Elijah took the child, and brought him down out of the chamber into the house, and delivered him unto his mother: and Elijah said, See, your son lives (1 Kings 17:23).
Surely I have behaved and quieted myself, as a child that is weaned of his mother: my soul is even as a weaned child (Psalms 131:2).
The rod and reproof give wisdom: but a child left to himself brings his mother to shame (Proverbs 29:15).
For before the child shall have knowledge to cry, My father, and my mother, the riches of Damascus and the spoil of Samaria shall be taken away before the king of Assyria (Isaiah 8:4).
When they were come into the house, they saw the young child with Mary His mother, and fell down, and worshipped Him: and when they had opened their treasures, they presented unto Him gifts; gold, and frankincense and myrrh (Matthew 2:11).
When they were departed, behold, the angel of the Lord appeared to Joseph in a dream, saying, Arise, and take the young child and His mother, and flee into Egypt, and be there until I bring you word: for Herod will seek the young child to destroy Him ((Matthew 2:13).
When he arose, he took the young child and His mother by night, and departed into Egypt (Matthew 2:14).
Saying, Arise, and take the young child and His mother, and go into the land: for they are dead which sought the young child's life (Matthew 2:20).
He arose, and took the young child and His mother, and came into the land (Matthew 2:21).
When they had fulfilled the days, as they returned, the child Jesus tarried behind in Jerusalem; and Joseph and his mother knew not of it (Luke 2:43).
   </Commentary>
  </BibleWord>  

  <AlphabetSequence>
   <SequenceOrderId>498</SequenceOrderId>
   <Word>A child and His mother.</Word>
   <AlphabetSequenceIndex>171</AlphabetSequenceIndex>
   <ScriptureReference>Genesis 7:11, Deuteronomy 18, Acts 1, Revelation 14:5</ScriptureReference>
   <ScriptureReferenceURI>http://bible.crosswalk.com/OnlineStudyBible/bible.cgi?new=1&amp;word=Genesis+7%3A11%2C+Deuteronomy+18%2C+Acts+1%2C+Revelation+14%3A5&amp;section=0&amp;version=nkj&amp;language=en</ScriptureReferenceURI>  
  </AlphabetSequence>

  <CaseBasedReasoning>
   <SequenceOrderId>1071</SequenceOrderId>
   <Commentary>
    Fremont Main Library 2400 Stevenson Blvd. Fremont CA 94538-2325. General Information: (510) 745-1400. http://www.aclibrary.org. 
    John Le Carre: Our Game, record bus passes on the left on Cherry street between Jasmine Avenue and Moores Avenue. Urine, right.
    880 South San Jose, Stevenson Blvd Exit: 2 birds fly across from the 880 North side.
    Scripture Reference Exodus 2:2, Hebrews 11:23-29: Fly towards the left; fly towards the right, fly towards the left.
    Reference Comforter_-_20030804IStillBelieveAndIAmEntrustedToYou_TurningBack_LearningToParticipate.xml Highway 84 Stevenson Blvd Exit: Full sun towards the right; half moon towards the left curved towards the right; Fly .. fly on the right wall. 
    8th day: (Genesis 17:12, Genesis 21:4, Leviticus 14:10, 2 Chronicles 29:17, Luke 2:21, Luke 9:28, John 20:26, Revelation 1:10) ... (Genesis 17:12, Genesis 21:4, Exodus 22:30, Leviticus 9:1, Leviticus 12:3, Leviticus 14:10, Leviticus 14:23, Leviticus 15:14, Leviticus 15:29, Leviticus 22:27, Leviticus 23:36, Leviticus 23:39, Numbers 6:10, Numbers 7:54, Numbers 29:35, 1 Kings 8:66, 2 Chronicles 7:9, 2 Chronicles 29:17, Nehemiah 8:18, Ezekiel 43:27, Luke 1:59, Luke 2:21, Luke 9:28, John 20:26, Acts 7:8, Philippians 3:5).
    UtilityDatabaseRelease20030812.cs: ScriptureReferenceURI() Retrieve the primary key column from the database schema and not from an external xml file; Eternal WeigthMeasure, sneeze; fly, flys right, left on top of top of the paper; fly, flys to the left.
   </Commentary>
  </CaseBasedReasoning>

  <!--
  <Export>
   <SequenceOrderId>25</SequenceOrderId>
   <Commentary></Commentary>
  </Export>
  -->

  <Software>
   <SequenceOrderId>247</SequenceOrderId>
   <Commentary>UtilityDatabaseRelease20030812.cs</Commentary>
  </Software>

  <ClassAssociates>
   <SequenceOrderId>285</SequenceOrderId>
   <Commentary>Return Top. Right door neighbor: go. Error, Highway 84 Stevenson Blvd Exit: Full sun towards the right; half moon towards the left curved towards the right.</Commentary>
  </ClassAssociates>

  </TheWord>
</wordOfGod>