<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type='text/xsl' href='TheWord.xslt'?>
<wordOfGod>
 <TheWord>

  <SequenceOrderId>68</SequenceOrderId>
  <Dated>2003-08-27T00:00:00.0000000-08:00</Dated>
  <FromUntil>239</FromUntil>
  <ScriptureReference>1 Samuel 2:35, 1 Chronicles 22:7, 1 Chronicles 28:9, Job 23:13, Isaiah 26:3, Lamentations 3:21, Matthew 22:37, Mark 12:30, Luke 10:27, Acts 17:11, Romans 8:27, Romans 12:16, Romans 15:5, Romans 15:6, 2 Corinthians 8:12, 2 Corinthians 13:11, Ephesians 4:23, Philippians 1:27, Philippians 2:2, Philippians 3:15, Philippians 3:16, Philippians 4:7, Colossians 3:12, 2 Timothy 1:7, 1 Peter 1:13, 1 Peter 3:8, 1 Peter 5:2, 2 Peter 3:1, 2 Peter 3:2</ScriptureReference>
  <ScriptureReferenceURI>http://bible.crosswalk.com/OnlineStudyBible/bible.cgi?new=1&amp;word=1+Samuel+2%3A35%2C+1+Chronicles+22%3A7%2C+1+Chronicles+28%3A9%2C+Job+23%3A13%2C+Isaiah+26%3A3%2C+Lamentations+3%3A21%2C+Matthew+22%3A37%2C+Mark+12%3A30%2C+Luke+10%3A27%2C+Acts+17%3A11%2C+Romans+8%3A27%2C+Romans+12%3A16%2C+Romans+15%3A5%2C+Romans+15%3A6%2C+2+Corinthians+8%3A12%2C+2+Corinthians+13%3A11%2C+Ephesians+4%3A23%2C+Philippians+1%3A27%2C+Philippians+2%3A2%2C+Philippians+3%3A15%2C+Philippians+3%3A16%2C+Philippians+4%3A7%2C+Colossians+3%3A12%2C+2+Timothy+1%3A7%2C+1+Peter+1%3A13%2C+1+Peter+3%3A8%2C+1+Peter+5%3A2%2C+2+Peter+3%3A1%2C+2+Peter+3%3A2&amp;section=0&amp;version=nkj&amp;language=en</ScriptureReferenceURI>
  <Title>Polishing the mind.</Title>

  <!--
  <Prophet>
   <SequenceOrderId>29</SequenceOrderId>
   <Commentary></Commentary>
   <ScriptureReference></ScriptureReference>
   <ScriptureReferenceURI></ScriptureReferenceURI>
  </Prophet>
  -->

  <Remember>
   <SequenceOrderId>360</SequenceOrderId>
   <DatedFrom>2003-08-01T00:00:00.0000000-08:00</DatedFrom>
   <DatedUntil>2003-08-27T00:00:00.0000000-08:00</DatedUntil>
   <ButtonGetGroupMembers>26</ButtonGetGroupMembers>
   <Commentary>The LORD said unto Moses, Make you a fiery serpent, and set it upon a pole: and it shall come to pass, that every one that is bitten, when he looks upon it, shall live (Numbers 21:8). Moses made a serpent of brass, and put it upon a pole, and it came to pass, that if a serpent had bitten any man, when he beheld the serpent of brass, he lived (Numbers 21:9).</Commentary>
   <Filename>Comforter_-_20030801Polish.xml</Filename>
   <ScriptureReference>Numbers 21:8, Numbers 21:9</ScriptureReference>
   <ScriptureReferenceURI>http://bible.crosswalk.com/OnlineStudyBible/bible.cgi?new=1&amp;word=Numbers+21%3A8%2C+Numbers+21%3A9&amp;section=0&amp;version=nkj&amp;language=en</ScriptureReferenceURI>
  </Remember>

  <!--
  <ScriptureReading>
   <SequenceOrderId>68</SequenceOrderId>
   <ScriptureReference></ScriptureReference>
   <ScriptureReferenceURI></ScriptureReferenceURI>
  </ScriptureReading>
  -->

  <!--
  <Sign>
   <SequenceOrderId>27</SequenceOrderId>
   <Measure></Measure>
   <ButtonGetGroupMembers></ButtonGetGroupMembers>
   <Commentary></Commentary>
   <ScriptureReference</ScriptureReference>
   <ScriptureReferenceURI></ScriptureReferenceURI>
  </Sign>
  -->

  <BibleWord>
   <SequenceOrderId>247</SequenceOrderId>
   <Word>Mind</Word>
   <Commentary>
I will raise Me up a faithful priest, that shall do according to that which is in Mine heart and in My mind: and I will build Him a sure house; and He shall walk before Mine anointed for ever (1 Samuel 2:35).
David said to Solomon, My son, as for me, it was in my mind to build an house unto the name of the LORD My God (1 Chronicles 22:7).
You, Solomon my son, know you the God of your father, and serve Him with a perfect heart and with a willing mind: for the LORD searches all hearts, and understands all the imaginations of the thoughts: if you seek Him, He will be found of You; but if you forsake Him, He will cast you off for ever (1 Chronicles 28:9).
But He is in one mind, and who can turn Him? and what His soul desires, even that He does (Job 23:13).
You will keep him in perfect peace, whose mind is stayed on you: because He trustes in you (Isaiah 26:3).
This I recall to my mind, therefore have I hope (Lamentations 3:21).
Jesus said unto him, You shall love the Lord your God with all your heart, and with all your soul, and with all your mind (Matthew 22:37).
You shall love the Lord your God with all your heart, and with all your soul, and with all your mind, and with all your strength: this is the first commandment (Mark 12:30).
He answering said, You shall love the Lord your God with all your heart, and with all your soul, and with all your strength, and with all your mind; and your neighbour as yourself (Luke 10:27).
These were more noble than those in Thessalonica, in that they received the word with all readiness of mind, and searched the scriptures daily, whether those things were so (Acts 17:11).
He that searches the hearts knows what is the mind of the Spirit, because he makes intercession for the saints according to the will of God (Romans 8:27).
Be of the same mind one toward another. Mind not high things, but condescend to men of low estate. Be not wise in your own conceits (Romans 12:16).
Now the God of patience and consolation grant you to be likeminded one toward another according to Christ Jesus (Romans 15:5).
That you may with one mind and one mouth glorify God, even the Father of our Lord Jesus Christ (Romans 15:6).
For if there be first a willing mind, it is accepted according to that a man has, and not according to that he has not (2 Corinthians 8:12).
Finally, brethren, farewell. Be perfect, be of good comfort, be of one mind, live in peace; and the God of love and peace shall be with you (2 Corinthians 13:11).
Be renewed in the spirit of your mind (Ephesians 4:23).
Only let your conversation be as it becomes the gospel of Christ: that whether I come and see you, or else be absent, I may hear of your affairs, that you stand fast in one spirit, with one mind striving together for the faith of the gospel (Philippians 1:27).
Fulfil you my joy, that you be likeminded, having the same love, being of one accord, of one mind (Philippians 2:2).
Let us therefore, as many as be perfect, be thus minded: and if in any thing you be otherwise minded, God shall reveal even this unto you (Philippians 3:15).
Nevertheless, whereto we have already attained, let us walk by the same rule, let us mind the same thing (Philippians 3:16).
The peace of God, which passes all understanding, shall keep your hearts and minds through Christ Jesus (Philippians 4:7).
Put on therefore, as the elect of God, holy and beloved, bowels of mercies, kindness, humbleness of mind, meekness, longsuffering (Colossians 3:12).
For God has not given us the spirit of fear; but of power, and of love, and of a sound mind (2 Timothy 1:7).
Wherefore gird up the loins of your mind, be sober, and hope to the end for the grace that is to be brought unto you at the revelation of Jesus Christ (1 Peter 1:13).
Finally, be you all of one mind, having compassion one of another, love as brethren, be pitiful, be courteous (1 Peter 3:8).
Feed the flock of God which is among you, taking the oversight thereof, not by constraint, but willingly; not for filthy lucre, but of a ready mind (1 Peter 5:2).
This second epistle, beloved, I now write unto you; in both which I stir up your pure minds by way of remembrance (2 Peter 3:1).
That you may be mindful of the words which were spoken before by the holy prophets, and of the commandment of us the apostles of the Lord and Saviour (2 Peter 3:2).
   </Commentary>
  </BibleWord>  

  <AlphabetSequence>
   <SequenceOrderId>555</SequenceOrderId>
   <Word>Polishing the mind.</Word>
   <AlphabetSequenceIndex>182</AlphabetSequenceIndex>
   <ScriptureReference>Genesis 7:22, Deuteronomy 29, John 11, Revelation 13:12</ScriptureReference>
   <ScriptureReferenceURI>http://bible.crosswalk.com/OnlineStudyBible/bible.cgi?new=1&amp;word=Genesis+7%3A22%2C+Deuteronomy+29%2C+John+11%2C+Revelation+13%3A12&amp;section=0&amp;version=nkj&amp;language=en</ScriptureReferenceURI>
   <Commentary>Naked. Wake-up Orientation: Nose blocked. Faeces: nail cut, sneeze twice on the 2nd nail, excreate on the 10th nail, right nose running.</Commentary>
  </AlphabetSequence>

  <CaseBasedReasoning>
   <SequenceOrderId>1109</SequenceOrderId>
   <Commentary>
    Naked. Wake-up Orientation: Nose blocked.
    Wake-up Orientation: Right knee, upright.
    Faeces: nail cut, sneeze twice on the 2nd nail, excreate on the 10th nail, right nose running.
    Menu: mouse.
    Generate the data definition language (DDL), Comforter_-_20030827DDLWordEngineering.sql.
    SQL script: sneeze thrice.
    Bulkcopy (BCP): sneeze twice.
    Stop the database on both computers, and transfer the data files on the right, HolySpirit, to the computer on the left, Comfort, restart the database.
    Food4Less 39966 Cedar Blvd Newark 94560 CA French Baguettes.
    Kokuho Rice U.S. #1 Extra Fancy New Crop Net Wt. 20LBS 9.07kg.
   </Commentary>
  </CaseBasedReasoning>

  <!--
  <Export>
   <SequenceOrderId>25</SequenceOrderId>
   <Commentary></Commentary>
  </Export>
  -->

  <!--
  <Software>
   <SequenceOrderId>256</SequenceOrderId>
   <Commentary></Commentary>
  </Software>
  -->
 
  <ClassAssociates>
   <SequenceOrderId>320</SequenceOrderId>
   <Commentary>
    Mouse menu ... Door noise ... Door noise: Caucasian lady walking a brown dog towards the right.
   </Commentary>
  </ClassAssociates>
  
  </TheWord>
</wordOfGod>