<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type='text/xsl' href='TheWord.xslt'?>
<wordOfGod>
 <TheWord>
  <SequenceOrderId>22</SequenceOrderId>
  <Dated>2003-08-04T00:00:00.0000000-08:00</Dated>
  <ScriptureReference>Matthew 2:9, Matthew 2:12-13, Matthew 10:14, Mark 5:20, Mark 9:40, Luke 1:23, Luke 2:29, Luke 2:37, Luke 5:10, Luke 5:25, Luke 9:4, Luke 9:6, Luke 10:35, Luke 10:42, Luke 11:36, Luke 21:21, Luke 24:12, John 5:15</ScriptureReference>
  <ScriptureReferenceURI>http://bible.crosswalk.com/OnlineStudyBible/bible.cgi?new=1&amp;word=Matthew+2%3A9%2C+Matthew+2%3A12-13%2C+Matthew+10%3A14%2C+Mark+5%3A20%2C+Mark+9%3A40%2C+Luke+1%3A23%2C+Luke+2%3A29%2C+Luke+2%3A37%2C+Luke+5%3A10%2C+Luke+5%3A25%2C+Luke+9%3A4%2C+Luke+9%3A6%2C+Luke+10%3A35%2C+Luke+10%3A42%2C+Luke+11%3A36%2C+Luke+21%3A21%2C+Luke+24%3A12%2C+John+5%3A15&amp;section=0&amp;version=nkj&amp;language=en</ScriptureReferenceURI>  
  <Title>I still believe ... and I am entrusted to You. Turning back. Learning to participate.</Title>
  <Commentary />
  <Keyword />

  <Remember>
   <SequenceOrderId>327</SequenceOrderId>
   <DatedFrom>2003-06-11T00:00:00.0000000-08:00</DatedFrom>
   <DatedUntil>2003-08-04T00:00:00.0000000-08:00</DatedUntil>
   <SignIndex>54</SignIndex>
   <Commentary />
   <Filename>Comforter_-_20030611InSpiteOfItAllIStillBelieveInGodIStillBelieveInPrayersAndIAmBlessed_DavidGum_WaKanRiWiPeWonSortOutAFewPiecesLoriIyanKanONiMoIkanToDe.xml</Filename>
  <ScriptureReference>
   Deuteronomy 9:5, 1 Kings 3:6, Job 8:6, Psalms 9:8, Psalms 11:7, Psalms 15:2, Psalms 36:10, Psalms 58:1, Psalms 92:15, Psalms 94:15, Proverbs 11:6, Proverbs 13:6, Isaiah 26:10
  </ScriptureReference>   
  <ScriptureReferenceURI>
   http://bible.crosswalk.com/OnlineStudyBible/bible.cgi?new=1&amp;word=Deuteronomy+9%3A5%2C+1+Kings+3%3A6%2C+Job+8%3A6%2C+Psalms+9%3A8%2C+Psalms+11%3A7%2C+Psalms+15%3A2%2C+Psalms+36%3A10%2C+Psalms+58%3A1%2C+Psalms+92%3A15%2C+Psalms+94%3A15%2C+Proverbs+11%3A6%2C+Proverbs+13%3A6%2C+Isaiah+26%3A10&amp;section=0&amp;version=nkj&amp;language=en
  </ScriptureReferenceURI>   
  </Remember>

  <!--
  <ScriptureReading>
   <SequenceOrderId>64</SequenceOrderId>
   <ScriptureReference></ScriptureReference>
   <ScriptureReferenceURI></ScriptureReferenceURI>
  </ScriptureReading>
  -->

  <!--
  <Sign>
   <SequenceOrderId>21</SequenceOrderId>
   <Measure>Day</Measure>
   <SignIndex></SignIndex>
   <Commentary />
   <ScriptureReference></ScriptureReference>
   <ScriptureReferenceURI></ScriptureReferenceURI>
  </Sign>
  -->

  <BibleWord>
   <SequenceOrderId>197</SequenceOrderId>
   <Word>Part (Gospel)</Word>
   <Commentary>
 When the wise men had heard the king, they departed; and, lo, the star, which they saw in the east, went before them, till it came and stood over where the young child was (Matthew 2:9).
 Being warned of God in a dream that they should not return to Herod, they departed into their own country another way. And when they were departed, behold, the angel of the Lord appeared to Joseph in a dream, saying, Arise, and take the young Child and His mother, and flee into Egypt, and be you there until I bring you word: for Herod will seek the young child to destroy Him (Matthew 2:12-13).
 Whosoever shall not receive you, nor hear your words, when you depart out of that house or city, shake off the dust of your feet (Matthew 10:14).
 He departed, and began to publish in Decapolis how great things Jesus had done for him: and all men did marvel (Mark 5:20).
 For he that is not against us is on our part (Mark 9:40).
 It came to pass, that, as soon as the days of his ministration were accomplished, he departed to his own house (Luke 1:23).
 LORD, now let Your servant depart in peace, according to Your word (Luke 2:29).
 She was a widow of about fourscore and four years, which departed not from the temple, but served God with fastings and prayers night and day (Luke 2:37).
 Jesus Christ answered and said unto them, He that has two coats, let him impart to him that has none; and he that has meat, let him do likewise (Luke 3:11).
 They beckoned unto their partners, which were in the other ship, that they should come and help them. And they came, and filled both the ships, so that they began to sink (Luke 5:7).
 So was also James, and John, the sons of Zebedee, which were partners with Simon. And Jesus said unto Simon, Fear not; from henceforth you shall catch men (Luke 5:10).
 Immediately he rose up before them, and took up that whereon he lay, and departed to his own house, glorifying God (Luke 5:25).
 Whatsoever house you enter into, there abide, and thence depart (Luke 9:4).
 They departed, and went through the towns, preaching the gospel, and healing every where (Luke 9:6).
 On the morrow when he departed, he took out two pence, and gave them to the host, and said unto him, Take care of him; and whatsoever thou spendest more, when I come again, I will repay you (Luke 10:35).
 But one thing is needful: and Mary has chosen that good part, which shall not be taken away from her (Luke 10:42).
 If your whole body therefore be full of light, having no part dark, the whole shall be full of light, as when the bright shining of a candle does give you light (Luke 11:36).
 Then let them which are in Judaea flee to the mountains; and let them which are in the midst of it depart out; and let not them that are in the countries enter thereinto (Luke 21:21).
 Then arose Peter, and ran unto the sepulchre; and stooping down, he beheld the linen clothes laid by themselves, and departed, wondering in himself at that which was come to pass (Luke 24:12).
 The man departed, and said it was Jesus, which had made him whole (John 5:15).
   </Commentary>
  </BibleWord>

  <AlphabetSequence>
   <SequenceOrderId>472</SequenceOrderId>
   <Word>I still believe ... and I am entrusted to You.</Word>
   <AlphabetSequenceIndex>405</AlphabetSequenceIndex>
   <ScriptureReference>Genesis 17:7, Ezra 2, Jeremiah 40, Jude 1:25</ScriptureReference>
   <ScriptureReferenceURI>http://bible.crosswalk.com/OnlineStudyBible/bible.cgi?new=1&amp;word=Genesis+17%3A7%2C+Ezra+2%2C+Jeremiah+40%2C+Jude+1%3A25&amp;section=0&amp;version=nkj&amp;language=en</ScriptureReferenceURI>  
  </AlphabetSequence>

  <AlphabetSequence>
   <SequenceOrderId>473</SequenceOrderId>
   <Word>Turning back.</Word>
   <AlphabetSequenceIndex>120</AlphabetSequenceIndex>
   <ScriptureReference>Genesis 5:14, Numbers 3, 1 Corinthians 8, Revelation 17:7</ScriptureReference>
   <ScriptureReferenceURI>http://bible.crosswalk.com/OnlineStudyBible/bible.cgi?new=1&amp;word=Genesis+5%3A14%2C+Numbers+3%2C+1+Corinthians+8%2C+Revelation+17%3A7&amp;section=0&amp;version=nkj&amp;language=en</ScriptureReferenceURI>  
  </AlphabetSequence>

  <AlphabetSequence>
   <SequenceOrderId>474</SequenceOrderId>
   <Word>Learning to participate.</Word>
   <AlphabetSequenceIndex>233</AlphabetSequenceIndex>
   <ScriptureReference>Genesis 9:27, Ruth 1, Matthew 28, Revelation 10:8</ScriptureReference>
   <ScriptureReferenceURI>http://bible.crosswalk.com/OnlineStudyBible/bible.cgi?new=1&amp;word=Genesis+9%3A27%2C+Ruth+1%2C+Matthew+28%2C+Revelation+10%3A8&amp;section=0&amp;version=nkj&amp;language=en</ScriptureReferenceURI>  
  </AlphabetSequence>

  <CaseBasedReasoning>
   <SequenceOrderId>1052</SequenceOrderId>
   <Commentary>
    Lake Blvd: 3 rounds. 1st round walking on Lake Blvd between Channel Drive and Ramsgate Drive, the birds are 17, 7, 19. 3rd round, towards the end of the 3rd leg, the birds are 2, 5, ... and the final bird will fly right upwards. 3rd round midway there are 7 birds towards the right.
    Highway 84 East towards 84 West Newark Blvd, the birds are 2, right outwards.
    5 Union City Blvd, Union City Transit Bus Stop (510) 471 1411: 2 birds towards the left.
    Train Track 27 Paseo Padre Parkway: Bird, orange, right.
    The intersection of Mallard CM 4750 and Spoonbill CM 34680 Nissan Sentra GXE Limited Edition 5 CHN784 Police Academy Pass the Torch RoundTree H.O.A. 34721 SpoonBill CM last building to the right. Walk back to record this incidence, and (2) sneeze at the intersection of Mallard CM and Canvasback Common.
    Chest, right, pain.
    Highway 84 Stevenson Blvd Exit: Full sun towards the right; half moon towards the left curved towards the right.
    Food4Less 39966 Cedar Blvd Newark 94560 CA French Baguettes.
    Kokuho Rice U.S. #1 Extra Fancy New Crop Net Wt. 20LBS 9.07kg.
    Merriam Webster''s Collegiate Dictionary Tenth Edition Merriam-Webster, Incorporated Springfield, Massachusetts, U.S.A. Entrust page 387, Entree 5th, Entrust 13th, 26 words on the right hand side.
   </Commentary>
  </CaseBasedReasoning>

  <!--
  <Export>
   <SequenceOrderId>24</SequenceOrderId>
   <Commentary></Commentary>
  </Export>
  -->

  <!--
  <Software>
   <SequenceOrderId>241</SequenceOrderId>
   <Commentary></Commentary>
  </Software>
  -->
  
  <ClassAssociates>
   <SequenceOrderId>269</SequenceOrderId>
   <Commentary>TheWord Comforter_-_20030803IAMAGodThatUnderstands_TrainedInTheActOfGod.xml: System Exception. Noise. The intersection of Mallard CM 4750 and Spoonbill CM 34680 Nissan Sentra GXE Limited Edition 5 CHN784 Police Academy Pass the Torch RoundTree H.O.A. 34721 SpoonBill CM last building to the right. Explorer error. Reboot. Highway 84 East towards 8(5)4 West. Train Track 27 Paseo Padre Pa(c)r. XCopy Comforter_-_20030804IStillBelieveAndIAmEntrustedToYou_TurningBack_LearningToParticipate*.* A: Explorer Memory Error. Error, Highway 84 Stevenson Blvd Exit: Full sun towards the right; half moon towards the left curved towards the right.</Commentary>
  </ClassAssociates>

  </TheWord>
</wordOfGod>