<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type='text/xsl' href='TheWord.xslt'?>
<wordOfGod>
 <TheWord>

  <SequenceOrderId>187</SequenceOrderId>
  <Dated>2003-10-07T00:00:00.0000000-08:00</Dated>
  <ScriptureReference>Genesis 43:9, Exodus 19:5, Exodus 19:6, Exodus 34:2, 2 Samuel 13:13, 2 Kings 10:6, Psalms 41:10, Psalms 119:58, Isaiah 29:2, Isaiah 55:11, Jeremiah 15:18, Jeremiah 24:7, Lamentations 1:12, Micah 5:2, Luke 1:38, Acts 1:8, 1 Corinthians 9:15, Galatians 2:9</ScriptureReference>
  <ScriptureReferenceURI>http://bible.crosswalk.com/OnlineStudyBible/bible.cgi?new=1&amp;word=Genesis+43%3A9%2C+Exodus+19%3A5%2C+Exodus+19%3A6%2C+Exodus+34%3A2%2C+2+Samuel+13%3A13%2C+2+Kings+10%3A6%2C+Psalms+41%3A10%2C+Psalms+119%3A58%2C+Isaiah+29%3A2%2C+Isaiah+55%3A11%2C+Jeremiah+15%3A18%2C+Jeremiah+24%3A7%2C+Lamentations+1%3A12%2C+Micah+5%3A2%2C+Luke+1%3A38%2C+Acts+1%3A8%2C+1+Corinthians+9%3A15%2C+Galatians+2%3A9&amp;section=0&amp;version=nkj&amp;language=en</ScriptureReferenceURI>
  <Title>Be unto Me.</Title>

  <!--
  <JehovahRophe>
   <SequenceOrderId>10</SequenceOrderId>
   <Commentary></Commentary>
  </JehovahRophe>
  -->

  <!--
  <Dream>
   <SequenceOrderId>6</SequenceOrderId>
   <Commentary></Commentary>
  </Dream>
  -->

  <Prophet>
   <SequenceOrderId>87</SequenceOrderId>
   <Commentary>
I will be surety for him; of my hand shall you require him: if I bring him not unto you, and set him before you, then let me bear the blame for ever (Genesis 43:9).
Now therefore, if you will obey My voice indeed, and keep My covenant, then you shall be a peculiar treasure unto Me above all people: for all the earth is Mine (Exodus 19:5).
You shall be unto Me a kingdom of priests, and an holy nation. These are the words which you shall speak unto the children of Israel (Exodus 19:6).
Be ready in the morning, and come up in the morning unto mount Sinai, and present yourself there to Me in the top of the mount (Exodus 34:2).
I, whither shall I cause my shame to go? and as for you, You shall be as one of the fools in Israel. Now therefore, I pray you, speak unto the king; for he will not withhold me from you (2 Samuel 13:13).
Then he wrote a letter the second time to them, saying, If you be mine, and if you will hearken unto my voice, take you the heads of the men your master's sons, and come to me to Jezreel by to morrow this time. Now the king's sons, being seventy persons, were with the great men of the city, which brought them up (2 Kings 10:6). 
But You, O LORD, be merciful unto me, and raise me up, that I may requite them (Psalms 41:10).
I intreated Your favour with my whole heart: be merciful unto me according to Your word (Psalms 119:58).
Yet I will distress Ariel, and there shall be heaviness and sorrow: and it shall be unto Me as Ariel (Isaiah 29:2).
So shall My word be that goes forth out of My mouth: it shall not return unto me void, but it shall accomplish that which I please, and it shall prosper in the thing whereto I sent it (Isaiah 55:11).
Why is my pain perpetual, and my wound incurable, which refuses to be healed? will you be altogether unto me as a liar, and as waters that fail? (Jeremiah 15:18).
I will give them an heart to know Me, that I am the LORD: and they shall be My people, and I will be their God: for they shall return unto Me with their whole heart (Jeremiah 24:7).
Is it nothing to you, all you that pass by? behold, and see if there be any sorrow like unto my sorrow, which is done unto me, wherewith the LORD has afflicted me in the day of His fierce anger (Lamentations 1:12).
But you, Bethlehem Ephratah, though you be little among the thousands of Judah, yet out of you shall He come forth unto Me that is to be ruler in Israel; whose goings forth have been from of old, from everlasting (Micah 5:2).
Mary said, Behold the handmaid of the Lord; be it unto me according to Your word. And the angel departed from her (Luke 1:38).
But you shall receive power, after that the Holy Ghost is come upon you: and you shall be witnesses unto Me both in Jerusalem, and in all Judaea, and in Samaria, and unto the uttermost part of the earth (Acts 1:8).
But I have used none of these things: neither have I written these things, that it should be so done unto me: for it were better for me to die, than that any man should make my glorying void (1 Corinthians 9:15).
When James, Cephas, and John, who seemed to be pillars, perceived the grace that was given unto me, they gave to me and Barnabas the right hands of fellowship; that we should go unto the heathen, and they unto the circumcision (Galatians 2:9).
   </Commentary>
  </Prophet>

  <Remember>
   <SequenceOrderId>431</SequenceOrderId>
   <DatedFrom>2003-09-26T00:00:00.0000000-08:00</DatedFrom>
   <DatedUntil>2003-10-07T00:00:00.0000000-08:00</DatedUntil>
   <FromUntil>11</FromUntil>
   <Commentary>How blessed is the Man that has made God His shelter? I AM so glad You so know Me. Everyday I AM so glad its Jesus. Everyday I AM so glad its Christ. Everyday the day is crying, the heaven is singing, Send the Savior's Son.</Commentary>
   <ScriptureReference>Matthew 1:16, Matthew 16:20, Matthew 26:63, Matthew 27:17, Matthew 27:22, Mark 12:35, John 20:31, Acts 2:36, Acts 18:5, Acts 18:28, Romans 8:11, 1 John 2:22, 1 John 5:1, Revelation 20:4</ScriptureReference>
   <ScriptureReferenceURI>http://bible.crosswalk.com/OnlineStudyBible/bible.cgi?new=1&amp;word=Matthew+1%3A16%2C+Matthew+16%3A20%2C+Matthew+26%3A63%2C+Matthew+27%3A17%2C+Matthew+27%3A22%2C+Mark+12%3A35%2C+John+20%3A31%2C+Acts+2%3A36%2C+Acts+18%3A5%2C+Acts+18%3A28%2C+Romans+8%3A11%2C+1+John+2%3A22%2C+1+John+5%3A1%2C+Revelation+20%3A4&amp;section=0&amp;version=nkj&amp;language=en</ScriptureReferenceURI>
   <Filename>Comforter_-_20030926HowBlessedIsTheManThatHasMadeGodHisShelter_IAMSoGladYouSoKnowMe_EverydayIAMSoGladItsJesusEverydayIAMSoGladItsChrist_EverydayTheDayIsCryingTheHeavenIsSingingSendTheSavior'sSon.xml</Filename>
  </Remember>

  <!--
  <ScriptureReading>
   <SequenceOrderId>77</SequenceOrderId>
   <ScriptureReference></ScriptureReference>
   <ScriptureReferenceURI></ScriptureReferenceURI>
  </ScriptureReading>
  -->

  <!--
  <Sign>
   <SequenceOrderId>35</SequenceOrderId>
   <Measure></Measure>
   <SignIndex></SignIndex>
   <Commentary></Commentary>
   <ScriptureReference></ScriptureReference>
   <ScriptureReferenceURI></ScriptureReferenceURI>
  </Sign>
  -->

  <BibleWord>
   <SequenceOrderId>367</SequenceOrderId>
   <Word> Be ... Unto ... Me </Word>
  </BibleWord>

  <AlphabetSequence>
   <SequenceOrderId>775</SequenceOrderId>
   <Word>Be unto Me.</Word>
   <AlphabetSequenceIndex>95</AlphabetSequenceIndex>
   <ScriptureReference>Genesis 4:15, Leviticus 5, Galatians 4, Revelation 18:14</ScriptureReference>
   <ScriptureReferenceURI>http://bible.crosswalk.com/OnlineStudyBible/bible.cgi?new=1&amp;word=Genesis+4%3A15%2C+Leviticus+5%2C+Galatians+4%2C+Revelation+18%3A14&amp;section=0&amp;version=nkj&amp;language=en</ScriptureReferenceURI>
  </AlphabetSequence>

  <CaseBasedReasoning>
   <SequenceOrderId>1223</SequenceOrderId>
   <Commentary>Fremont Main Library 2400 Stevenson Blvd. Fremont CA 94538-2325. Address SequenceOrderId 107 Washington High School 38442 Fremont Boulevard: Right armpit sweat flows through the right side. Campus Crusade for Christ at California State University, Hayward http://www.csuhcrusade.org: Direction and Schedule. Turn on the computer: Left hand twitches. Kokuho Rice U.S. #1 Extra Fancy New Crop Net Wt. 20LBS 9.07kg: 2 cookings. Turn on the computer: Left hand twitches. Kokuho Rice U.S. #1 Extra Fancy New Crop Net Wt. 20LBS 9.07kg. Software 268: Comforter_-_20030926Christ.xml ... fly flys towards the left.</Commentary>
  </CaseBasedReasoning>

  <!--
  <Export>
   <SequenceOrderId>26</SequenceOrderId>
   <Commentary></Commentary>
  </Export>
  -->

  <Software>
   <SequenceOrderId>268</SequenceOrderId>
   <Commentary>Comforter_-_20030926Christ.xml</Commentary>
  </Software>

  <ClassAssociates>
   <SequenceOrderId>422</SequenceOrderId>
   <Commentary>Campus Crusade for Christ at California State University, Hayward http://www.csuhcrusade.org ... Internet Explorer (IE) error.  Adobe Acrobat ... error ... Address Query greater than or equal to 20030706 ... Explorer error.  Contact Export: Comforter_-_20031007Contact.txt ... left hand twitches. Right next door neighbor: Is it worth it? Turn on the computer: Left hand twitches ... Smell. Turn on the computer: Left hand twitches ... Smell. CaseBasedReasoning 1223: Left hand twitches ... Smell ... CaseBasedReasoning 1223: Fremont Library ... Smell. Record Address SequenceOrderId 107 Washington High School 38442 Fremont Boulevard: User Interface (UI) error, smell. Remember 431: Explorer ... Monitor noise. CaseBasedReasoning 1223: Kokuho Rice U.S. #1 Extra Fancy New Crop Net Wt. 20LBS 9.07kg ... smell. Software 268: Comforter_-_20030926Christ.xml ... sm(e)ll ...</Commentary>  
  </ClassAssociates>

  </TheWord>
</wordOfGod>