<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type='text/xsl' href='TheWord.xslt'?>
<wordOfGod>
 <TheWord>

  <SequenceOrderId>197</SequenceOrderId>
  <Dated>2003-10-13T00:00:00.0000000-08:00</Dated>
  <ScriptureReference>Numbers 26:3, Numbers 26:63, Numbers 31:12, Numbers 32:29, Numbers 33:50, Numbers 35:1, Numbers 36:13, Deuteronomy 1:1, Deuteronomy 4:41, Joshua 1:2, Joshua 1:14, Joshua 1:15, Joshua 13:8, Joshua 13:32, Joshua 14:3, Joshua 22:4, Joshua 22:7</ScriptureReference>
  <ScriptureReferenceURI>http://bible.crosswalk.com/OnlineStudyBible/bible.cgi?new=1&amp;word=Numbers+26%3A3%2C+Numbers+26%3A63%2C+Numbers+31%3A12%2C+Numbers+32%3A29%2C+Numbers+33%3A50%2C+Numbers+35%3A1%2C+Numbers+36%3A13%2C+Deuteronomy+1%3A1%2C+Deuteronomy+4%3A41%2C+Joshua+1%3A2%2C+Joshua+1%3A14%2C+Joshua+1%3A15%2C+Joshua+13%3A8%2C+Joshua+13%3A32%2C+Joshua+14%3A3%2C+Joshua+22%3A4%2C+Joshua+22%3A7&amp;section=0&amp;version=nkj&amp;language=en</ScriptureReferenceURI>
  <Title>Lady Life.</Title>
  <FromUntil>286</FromUntil>

  <!--
  <JehovahRophe>
   <SequenceOrderId>11</SequenceOrderId>
   <Commentary></Commentary>
  </JehovahRophe>
  -->

  <!--
  <Dream>
   <SequenceOrderId>6</SequenceOrderId>
   <Commentary></Commentary>
  </Dream>
  -->

  <Prophet>
   <SequenceOrderId>96</SequenceOrderId>
   <Commentary>
    Moses and Eleazar the priest spoke with them in the plains of Moab by Jordan near Jericho, saying, (Numbers 26:3).
    These are they that were numbered by Moses and Eleazar the priest, who numbered the children of Israel in the plains of Moab by Jordan near Jericho (Numbers 26:63).
    They brought the captives, and the prey, and the spoil, unto Moses, and Eleazar the priest, and unto the congregation of the children of Israel, unto the camp at the plains of Moab, which are by Jordan near Jericho (Numbers 31:12).
    Moses said unto them, If the children of Gad and the children of Reuben will pass with you over Jordan, every man armed to battle, before the LORD, and the land shall be subdued before you; then you shall give them the land of Gilead for a possession: (Numbers 32:29). 
    The LORD spoke unto Moses in the plains of Moab by Jordan near Jericho, saying, (Numbers 33:50).
    The LORD spoke unto Moses in the plains of Moab by Jordan near Jericho, saying, (Numbers 35:1).
    These are the commandments and the judgments, which the LORD commanded by the hand of Moses unto the children of Israel in the plains of Moab by Jordan near Jericho (Numbers 36:13).
    These be the words which Moses spoke unto all Israel on this side Jordan in the wilderness, in the plain over against the Red sea, between Paran, and Tophel, and Laban, and Hazeroth, and Dizahab (Deuteronomy 1:1).
    Then Moses severed three cities on this side Jordan toward the sunrising; (Deuteronomy 4:41). 
    Moses My servant is dead; now therefore arise, go over this Jordan, you, and all this people, unto the land which I do give to them, even to the children of Israel (Joshua 1:2).
    Your wives, your little ones, and your cattle, shall remain in the land which Moses gave you on this side Jordan; but you shall pass before your brethren armed, all the mighty men of valor, and help them; (Joshua 1:14). 
    Until the LORD have given your brethren rest, as He has given you, and they also have possessed the land which the LORD your God gives them: then you shall return unto the land of your possession, and enjoy it, which Moses the LORD's servant gave you on this side Jordan toward the sunrising (Joshua 1:15). 
    With whom the Reubenites and the Gadites have received their inheritance, which Moses gave them, beyond Jordan eastward, even as Moses the servant of the LORD gave them; (Joshua 13:8). 
    These are the countries which Moses did distribute for inheritance in the plains of Moab, on the other side Jordan, by Jericho, eastward (Joshua 13:32). 
    For Moses had given the inheritance of two tribes and an half tribe on the other side Jordan: but unto the Levites he gave none inheritance among them (Joshua 14:3). 
    Now the LORD your God has given rest unto your brethren, as He promised them: therefore now return you, and get you unto your tents, and unto the land of your possession, which Moses the servant of the LORD gave you on the other side Jordan (Joshua 22:4). 
    Now to the one half of the tribe of Manasseh Moses had given possession in Bashan: but unto the other half thereof gave Joshua among their brethren on this side Jordan westward. And when Joshua sent them away also unto their tents, then he blessed them, (Joshua 22:7). 
   </Commentary>
  </Prophet>

  <!--
  <Remember>
   <SequenceOrderId>439</SequenceOrderId>
   <DatedFrom></DatedFrom>
   <DatedUntil></DatedUntil>
   <FromUntil></FromUntil>
   <Commentary></Commentary>
   <ScriptureReference></ScriptureReference>
   <ScriptureReferenceURI></ScriptureReferenceURI>
   <Filename></Filename>
  </Remember>
  -->

  <!--
  <ScriptureReading>
   <SequenceOrderId>79</SequenceOrderId>
   <ScriptureReference></ScriptureReference>
   <ScriptureReferenceURI></ScriptureReferenceURI>
  </ScriptureReading>
  -->

  <!--
  <Sign>
   <SequenceOrderId>35</SequenceOrderId>
   <Measure></Measure>
   <SignIndex></SignIndex>
   <Commentary></Commentary>
   <ScriptureReference></ScriptureReference>
   <ScriptureReferenceURI></ScriptureReferenceURI>
  </Sign>
  -->

  <BibleWord>
   <SequenceOrderId>379</SequenceOrderId>
   <Word>Moses ... Jordan</Word>
  </BibleWord>

  <AlphabetSequence>
   <SequenceOrderId>783</SequenceOrderId>
   <Word>Lady Life.</Word>
   <AlphabetSequenceIndex>74</AlphabetSequenceIndex>
   <ScriptureReference>Genesis 3:18, Exodus 24, 1 Thessalonians 5, Revelation 19:11</ScriptureReference>
   <ScriptureReferenceURI>http://bible.crosswalk.com/OnlineStudyBible/bible.cgi?new=1&amp;word=Genesis+3%3A18%2C+Exodus+24%2C+1+Thessalonians+5%2C+Revelation+19%3A11&amp;section=0&amp;version=nkj&amp;language=en</ScriptureReferenceURI>
  </AlphabetSequence>

  <CaseBasedReasoning>
   <SequenceOrderId>1237</SequenceOrderId>
   <Commentary>Wake-up Orientation: Erection. Wake-up Orientation: Left Knee upright. Wake-up Orientation: Feets crossed. Turn on the computer: both fingers twitches ... Urine: Falls on the left side of the right feet. Delete the WordEngineering backup files. Empty the Recycle Bin. Delete the bulkcopy files between 20031001 and 20031009. Empty the Recycle Bin. Kokuho Rice U.S. #1 Extra Fancy New Crop Net Wt. 20LBS 9.07kg.</Commentary>
  </CaseBasedReasoning>

  <!--
  <Export>
   <SequenceOrderId>26</SequenceOrderId>
   <Commentary></Commentary>
  </Export>
  -->

  <!--
  <Software>
   <SequenceOrderId>274</SequenceOrderId>
   <Commentary></Commentary>
  </Software>
  -->  

  <ClassAssociates>
   <SequenceOrderId>437</SequenceOrderId>
   <Commentary>Shutdown the left computer, Comfort ... Comfort computer noise. Turn on the computer: Smell ... Left fingers twitches ... Keyboard error. CaseBasedReasoning 1237 No(s)de Empty: Keyboard (r)Error. Shutdown the left computer, Comfort ... Comfort: Smell. Prophet 96: Moses ... Jordan ... Keyboard error ... Clipboard CutPaste(r) error. Prophet 96: Update error.</Commentary> 
  </ClassAssociates>

  </TheWord>
</wordOfGod>