<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type='text/xsl' href='TheWord.xslt'?>
<wordOfGod>
 <TheWord>

  <SequenceOrderId>60</SequenceOrderId>
  <Dated>2003-08-23T00:00:00.0000000-08:00</Dated>
  <ScriptureReference>Exodus 10:17, Deuteronomy 2:37, Deuteronomy 15:5, Deuteronomy 28:13, Joshua 1:17, Joshua 13:14, 1 Kings 14:13, 1 Chronicles 22:12, Psalms 62:5, Ecclesiastes 7:29, Jeremiah 3:13, John 3:18, John 5:18, John 11:52, John 17:3, Acts 19:27, Romans 5:11, 2 Corinthians 9:12, Colossians 4:11, 1 Thessalonians 1:8, 1 Timothy 1:17, Jude 1:25, Revelation 9:4, Genesis 9:3, Joshua 22, Luke 8, Revelation 12:2</ScriptureReference>
  <ScriptureReferenceURI>http://bible.crosswalk.com/OnlineStudyBible/bible.cgi?new=1&amp;word=Exodus+10%3A17%2C+Deuteronomy+2%3A37%2C+Deuteronomy+15%3A5%2C+Deuteronomy+28%3A13%2C+Joshua+1%3A17%2C+Joshua+13%3A14%2C+1+Kings+14%3A13%2C+1+Chronicles+22%3A12%2C+Psalms+62%3A5%2C+Ecclesiastes+7%3A29%2C+Jeremiah+3%3A13%2C+John+3%3A18%2C+John+5%3A18%2C+John+11%3A52%2C+John+17%3A3%2C+Acts+19%3A27%2C+Romans+5%3A11%2C+2+Corinthians+9%3A12%2C+Colossians+4%3A11%2C+1+Thessalonians+1%3A8%2C+1+Timothy+1%3A17%2C+Jude+1%3A25%2C+Revelation+9%3A4%2C+Genesis+9%3A3%2C+Joshua+22%2C+Luke+8%2C+Revelation+12%3A2&amp;section=0&amp;version=nkj&amp;language=en</ScriptureReferenceURI>
  <Title>Only God can make Me rise.</Title>
  <Commentary>But as for me, this secret is not revealed to me for any wisdom that I have more than any living, but for their sakes that shall make known the interpretation to the king, and that you might know the thoughts of your heart (Daniel 2:30).</Commentary>

  <Prophet>
   <SequenceOrderId>23</SequenceOrderId>
   <Commentary>
    But as for me, this secret is not revealed to me for any wisdom that I have more than any living, but for their sakes that shall make known the interpretation to the king, and that you might know the thoughts of your heart (Daniel 2:30).
    Only unto the land of the children of Ammon you came not, nor unto any place of the river Jabbok, nor unto the cities in the mountains, nor unto whatsoever the LORD our God forbade us (Deuteronomy 2:37).
    Not for that nation only, but that also He should gather together in one the children of God that were scattered abroad (John 11:52).
    It was commanded them that they should not hurt the grass of the earth, neither any green thing, neither any tree; but only those men which have not the seal of God in their foreheads (Revelation 9:4).
   </Commentary>
   <ScriptureReference>Daniel 2:30, Deuteronomy 2:37, John 11:52, Revelation 9:4</ScriptureReference>   
   <ScriptureReferenceURI>http://bible.crosswalk.com/OnlineStudyBible/bible.cgi?new=1&amp;word=Daniel+2%3A30%2C+Deuteronomy+2%3A37%2C+John+11%3A52%2C+Revelation+9%3A4&amp;section=0&amp;version=nkj&amp;language=en</ScriptureReferenceURI>
  </Prophet>

  <!--
  <Remember>
   <SequenceOrderId>356</SequenceOrderId>
   <DatedFrom></DatedFrom>
   <DatedUntil></DatedUntil>
   <FromUntil></FromUntil>
   <Commentary></Commentary>
   <Filename></Filename>
   <ScriptureReference></ScriptureReference>   
   <ScriptureReferenceURI></ScriptureReferenceURI>
  </Remember>
  -->

  <!--
  <ScriptureReading>
   <SequenceOrderId>67</SequenceOrderId>
   <ScriptureReference></ScriptureReference>
   <ScriptureReferenceURI></ScriptureReferenceURI>
  </ScriptureReading>
  -->

  <!--
  <Sign>
   <SequenceOrderId>27</SequenceOrderId>
   <Measure></Measure>
   <FromUntil></FromUntil>
   <Commentary></Commentary>
   <ScriptureReference</ScriptureReference>
   <ScriptureReferenceURI></ScriptureReferenceURI>
  </Sign>
  -->

  <BibleWord>
   <SequenceOrderId>238</SequenceOrderId>
   <Word>Only ... God</Word>
   <Commentary>
Now therefore forgive, I pray you, my sin only this once, and entreat the LORD your God, that He may take away from me this death only (Exodus 10:17).
Only unto the land of the children of Ammon you came not, nor unto any place of the river Jabbok, nor unto the cities in the mountains, nor unto whatsoever the LORD our God forbade us (Deuteronomy 2:37).
Only if you carefully hearken unto the voice of the LORD your God, to observe to do all these commandments which I command you this day (Deuteronomy 15:5).
The LORD shall make you the head, and not the tail; and you shall be above only, and you shall not be beneath; if that you hearken unto the commandments of the LORD your God, which I command you this day, to observe and to do them (Deuteronomy 28:13).
According as we hearkened unto Moses in all things, so will we hearken unto you: only the LORD your God be with you, as He was with Moses (Joshua 1:17).
Only unto the tribes of Levi he gave none inheritance; the sacrifices of the LORD God of Israel made by fire are their inheritance, as He said unto them (Joshua 13:14).
All Israel shall mourn for him, and bury him: for he only of Jeroboam shall come to the grave, because in him there is found some good thing toward the LORD God of Israel in the house of Jeroboam (1 Kings 14:13).
Only the LORD give you wisdom and understanding, and give you charge concerning Israel, that you may keep the law of the LORD your God (1 Chronicles 22:12).
My soul, wait you only upon God; for my expectation is from him (Psalms 62:5).
Lo, this only have I found, that God has made man upright; but they have sought out many inventions (Ecclesiastes 7:29).
Only acknowledge your iniquity, that you have transgressed against the LORD your God, and has scattered your ways to the strangers under every green tree, and you have not obeyed My voice, said the LORD (Jeremiah 3:13).
He that believes on him is not condemned: but he that believes not is condemned already, because he has not believed in the name of the only begotten Son of God (John 3:18).
Therefore the Jews sought the more to kill him, because he not only had broken the sabbath, but said also that God was His Father, making Himself equal with God (John 5:18).
Not for that nation only, but that also He should gather together in one the children of God that were scattered abroad (John 11:52).
This is life eternal, that they might know You the only true God, and Jesus Christ, whom You have sent (John 17:3).
So that not only this our craft is in danger to be set at nought; but also that the temple of the great goddess Diana should be despised, and her magnificence should be destroyed, whom all Asia and the world worshipped (Acts 19:27).
Not only so, but we also joy in God through our Lord Jesus Christ, by whom we have now received the atonement (Romans 5:11).
For the administration of this service not only supplies the want of the saints, but is abundant also by many thanksgivings unto God (2 Corinthians 9:12).
Jesus, which is called Justus, who are of the circumcision. These only are my fellowworkers unto the kingdom of God, which have been a comfort unto me (Colossians 4:11).
For from you sounded out the word of the Lord not only in Macedonia and Achaia, but also in every place your faith to God-ward is spread abroad; so that we need not to speak any thing (1 Thessalonians 1:8).
Now unto the King eternal, immortal, invisible, the only wise God, be honour and glory for ever and ever. Amen (1 Timothy 1:17).
To the only wise God our Saviour, be glory and majesty, dominion and power, both now and ever. Amen (Jude 1:25).
It was commanded them that they should not hurt the grass of the earth, neither any green thing, neither any tree; but only those men which have not the seal of God in their foreheads (Revelation 9:4).
   </Commentary>
   <ScriptureReference>Exodus 10:17, Deuteronomy 2:37, Deuteronomy 15:5, Deuteronomy 28:13, Joshua 1:17, Joshua 13:14, 1 Kings 14:13, 1 Chronicles 22:12, Psalms 62:5, Ecclesiastes 7:29, Jeremiah 3:13, John 3:18, John 5:18, John 11:52, John 17:3, Acts 19:27, Romans 5:11, 2 Corinthians 9:12, Colossians 4:11, 1 Thessalonians 1:8, 1 Timothy 1:17, Jude 1:25, Revelation 9:4</ScriptureReference>
   <ScriptureReferenceURI>http://bible.crosswalk.com/OnlineStudyBible/bible.cgi?new=1&amp;word=Exodus+10%3A17%2C+Deuteronomy+2%3A37%2C+Deuteronomy+15%3A5%2C+Deuteronomy+28%3A13%2C+Joshua+1%3A17%2C+Joshua+13%3A14%2C+1+Kings+14%3A13%2C+1+Chronicles+22%3A12%2C+Psalms+62%3A5%2C+Ecclesiastes+7%3A29%2C+Jeremiah+3%3A13%2C+John+3%3A18%2C+John+5%3A18%2C+John+11%3A52%2C+John+17%3A3%2C+Acts+19%3A27%2C+Romans+5%3A11%2C+2+Corinthians+9%3A12%2C+Colossians+4%3A11%2C+1+Thessalonians+1%3A8%2C+1+Timothy+1%3A17%2C+Jude+1%3A25%2C+Revelation+9%3A4&amp;section=0&amp;version=nkj&amp;language=en</ScriptureReferenceURI>
  </BibleWord>  

  <AlphabetSequence>
   <SequenceOrderId>524</SequenceOrderId>
   <Word>Only God can make Me rise.</Word>
   <AlphabetSequenceIndex>209</AlphabetSequenceIndex>
   <ScriptureReference>Genesis 9:3, Joshua 22, Luke 8, Revelation 12:2</ScriptureReference>
   <ScriptureReferenceURI>http://bible.crosswalk.com/OnlineStudyBible/bible.cgi?new=1&amp;word=Genesis+9%3A3%2C+Joshua+22%2C+Luke+8%2C+Revelation+12%3A2&amp;section=0&amp;version=nkj&amp;language=en</ScriptureReferenceURI>  
  </AlphabetSequence>

  <CaseBasedReasoning>
   <SequenceOrderId>1100</SequenceOrderId>
   <Commentary>
    Fremont Main Library 2400 Stevenson Blvd. Fremont CA 94538-2325. General Information: (510) 745-1400. http://www.aclibrary.org.
    Quality Web Systems: qualitywebsys.com.
    Matthew MacDonald: ASP.NET The Complete Reference http://www.prosetech.com/completereference/ ISBN 0-07-219513-4 (C# supports an out parameter page 48).
    Assemblies of God: www.ag.org.
    Nation of Islam: www.noi.org.
    Society of Biblical Literature: www.sbl-site.org.
    George M. Stephenson: The religious Aspects of Swedish Immigration Library of Congress Catalog Card No 69-18790 Associate Professor of History University of Minnesota Minneapolis The University of Minnesota Press 1932 (200308231630 Return to the book shelf).
    John L. Allen, Jr.: Conclave ISBN 0-385-50453-5 (Chapter 3, page 69, restroom, right nose running) (In 1978, the Sala Bologna was used, page 81, left nose running) (Sistine Chapel and Casa Santa Marta, page 102, left nose running) (page 118...).
    Urine: right knee.
    Food4Less 39966 Cedar Blvd Newark 94560 CA French Baguettes.
    TheWordRelease20030823.xslt: Extend the column span for the prophet table header from 3 to 4.
    Butterfly, kitchen sink top left.
   </Commentary>
  </CaseBasedReasoning>

  <!--
  <Export>
   <SequenceOrderId>25</SequenceOrderId>
   <Commentary></Commentary>
  </Export>
  -->

  <Software>
   <SequenceOrderId>254</SequenceOrderId>
   <Commentary>TheWordRelease20030823.xslt Comforter_-_20030823Christ.xml Comforter_-_20030823WordEngineering.xml</Commentary>
  </Software>

  <!--
  <ClassAssociates>
   <SequenceOrderId>313</SequenceOrderId>
   <Commentary></Commentary>
  </ClassAssociates>
  -->
  
  </TheWord>
</wordOfGod>