<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type='text/xsl' href='TheWord.xslt'?>
<wordOfGod>
 <TheWord>
  <SequenceOrderId>7</SequenceOrderId>
  <Dated>2003-07-28T00:00:00.0000000-08:00</Dated>
  <ScriptureReference>Numbers 5:7, Numbers 5:8, Jeremiah 16:18, Jeremiah 50:29, Ezekiel 7:3, Ezekiel 7:4, Ezekiel 7:8, Ezekiel 7:9, Ezekiel 9:10, Ezekiel 11:21, Ezekiel 16:43, Ezekiel 22:31, Hosea 12:2, Joel 3:4</ScriptureReference>
  <ScriptureReferenceURI>http://bible.crosswalk.com/OnlineStudyBible/bible.cgi?new=1&amp;word=Numbers+5%3A7%2C+Numbers+5%3A8%2C+Jeremiah+16%3A18%2C+Jeremiah+50%3A29%2C+Ezekiel+7%3A3%2C+Ezekiel+7%3A4%2C+Ezekiel+7%3A8%2C+Ezekiel+7%3A9%2C+Ezekiel+9%3A10%2C+Ezekiel+11%3A21%2C+Ezekiel+16%3A43%2C+Ezekiel+22%3A31%2C+Hosea+12%3A2%2C+Joel+3%3A4&amp;section=0&amp;version=nkj&amp;language=en</ScriptureReferenceURI>
  <Title>Safwan Alamad.</Title>
  <Keyword />
  
  <Remember>
   <SequenceOrderId>315</SequenceOrderId>
   <DatedFrom>2002-08-31T00:00:00.0000000-08:00</DatedFrom>
   <DatedUntil>2003-07-28T00:00:00.0000000-08:00</DatedUntil>
   <SignIndex>331</SignIndex>
   <Commentary>Footmen Financial Flirtation? Fantasy Waterfall.</Commentary>
   <Filename>Comforter_-_20020831FootmenFinancialFlirtatationFantasyWaterfall.html</Filename>
   <ScriptureReference>Jeremiah 12:5, Jeremiah 49:19, Jeremiah 50:44, Matthew 3:6</ScriptureReference>
   <ScriptureReferenceURI>http://bible.crosswalk.com/OnlineStudyBible/bible.cgi?new=1&amp;word=Jeremiah+12%3A5%2C+Jeremiah+49%3A19%2C+Jeremiah+50%3A44%2C+Matthew+3%3A6&amp;section=0&amp;version=nkj&amp;language=en</ScriptureReferenceURI>
  </Remember>

  <!--
  <ScriptureReading>
   <SequenceOrderId>63</SequenceOrderId>
   <ScriptureReference />
   <ScriptureReferenceURI />
  </ScriptureReading>
  -->

  <!--
  <Sign>
   <SequenceOrderId>19</SequenceOrderId>
   <Measure />
   <SignIndex />
   <Commentary />
   <ScriptureReference />
   <ScriptureReferenceURI />
  </Sign>
  -->

  <BibleWord>
   <SequenceOrderId>180</SequenceOrderId>
   <Word>Recompense</Word>
   <Commentary>
Then they shall confess their sin which they have done: and he shall recompense his trespass with the principal thereof, and add unto it the fifth part thereof, and give it unto him against whom he has trespassed (Numbers 5:7).
But if the man have no kinsman to recompense the trespass unto, let the trespass be recompensed unto the LORD, even to the priest; beside the ram of the atonement, whereby an atonement shall be made for him (Numbers 5:7).
First I will recompense their iniquity and their sin double; because they have defiled My land, they have filled mine inheritance with the carcases of their detestable and abominable things (Jeremiah 16:18).
Call together the archers against Babylon: all you that bend the bow, camp against it round about; let none thereof escape: recompense her according to her work; according to all that she has done, do unto her: for she has been proud against the LORD, against the Holy One (Jeremiah 50:29).
Now is the end come upon you, and I will send Mine anger upon you, and will judge you according to your ways, and will recompense upon you all your abominations (Ezekiel 7:3).
Mine eye shall not spare you, neither will I have pity: but I will recompense your ways upon you, and your abominations shall be in the midst of you: and you shall know that I am the LORD (Ezekiel 7:4).
Now will I shortly pour out my fury upon you, and accomplish Mine anger upon you: and I will judge you according to your ways, and will recompense you for all your abominations (Ezekiel 7:8).
Mine eye shall not spare, neither will I have pity: I will recompense you according to your ways and your abominations that are in the midst of you; and you shall know that I am the LORD that smiteth (Ezekiel 7:9).
As for Me also, Mine eye shall not spare, neither will I have pity, but I will recompense their way upon their head (Ezekiel 9:10).
But as for them whose heart walks after the heart of their detestable things and their abominations, I will recompense their way upon their own heads, said the Lord GOD (Ezekiel 11:21).
Because you have not remembered the days of your youth, but has fretted Me in all these things; behold, therefore I also will recompense your way upon your head, said the Lord GOD: and you shall not commit this lewdness above all your abominations (Ezekiel 16:43).
Therefore have I poured out Mine indignation upon them; I have consumed them with the fire of My wrath: their own way have I recompensed upon their heads, said the Lord GOD (Ezekiel 22:31).
The LORD has also a controversy with Judah, and will punish Jacob according to his ways; according to his doings will he recompense him (Hosea 12:2).
Yes, and what have you to do with Me, O Tyre, and Zidon, and all the coasts of Palestine? will you render Me a recompence? and if you recompense Me, swiftly and speedily will I return your recompence upon your own head (Joel 3:4).
   </Commentary>
  </BibleWord>

  <AlphabetSequence>
   <SequenceOrderId>454</SequenceOrderId>
   <Word>Safwan Alamad.</Word>
   <AlphabetSequenceIndex>813</AlphabetSequenceIndex>
   <ScriptureReference>Genesis 4:16, Leviticus 6, Galatians 3, Revelation 18:13</ScriptureReference>
   <ScriptureReferenceURI>http://bible.crosswalk.com/OnlineStudyBible/bible.cgi?new=1&amp;word=Genesis+4%3A16%2C+Leviticus+6%2C+Galatians+3%2C+Revelation+18%3A13&amp;section=0&amp;version=nkj&amp;language=en</ScriptureReferenceURI>  
  </AlphabetSequence>

  <CaseBasedReasoning>
   <SequenceOrderId>1027</SequenceOrderId>
   <Commentary>Shower: butterfly, behind, slap, but on the other side of the glass. Food4Less 39966 Cedar Blvd Newark 94560 CA French Baguettes. Kokuho Rice U.S. #1 Extra Fancy New Crop Net Wt. 20LBS 9.07kg. Rename the remember's sign to signindex, the floppy disk will fall down from the left computer.</Commentary>
  </CaseBasedReasoning>

  <CaseBasedReasoning>
   <SequenceOrderId>1028</SequenceOrderId>
   <Dated>2003-07-29T00:00:00.0000000-08:00</Dated>
   <Commentary>Wake-up Orientation: Feets crossed. Record: ClassAssociates, 252, sneeze.</Commentary>
  </CaseBasedReasoning>

  <!--
  <Export>
   <SequenceOrderId>23</SequenceOrderId>
   <Dated />
   <Commentary />
  </Export>
  -->

  <Software>
   <SequenceOrderId>233</SequenceOrderId>
   <Commentary>
    Comforter_-_20030729RectangleCirclePolygon.svg
    Comforter_-_20030729RectangleCirclePolygonAutomatedSVG.html
    Comforter_-_20030729RectangleCirclePolygonUsingViewBox.svg
    SvgStatic.aspx
    SvgSql.aspx
    UtilitySvg.cs
    XmlDocumentSvg.cs
    XmlDocumentSvg.mak
    XmlDocumentSvgBasic.aspx
    XmlDocumentSvgBasic.bat
    XmlDocumentSvgBasic.html
    XmlDocumentSvgBasic.js
    XmlDocumentSvgBasicGZIPCompression.aspx
    XmlDocumentSvgBuild.bat
    XmlDocumentSvgDocument.xml 
   </Commentary>
  </Software>

  <ClassAssociates>
   <SequenceOrderId>252</SequenceOrderId>
   <Commentary>Kokuho Rice U.S. #1 Extra Fancy New Crop Net Wt. 20LBS 9.07kg.: Noise Kirkland Signature by Whirlpool Corporation. Model: SS22AEXHW01. Serial No. SK2643921. Manufacture Date: 06-00. Manufactured for Costco Wholesale Corporation by Whirlpool Corporation. Whirlpool Corporation. Benton Harbor, MI 49022. CaseBasedReasoing: 1028 Wake-up (O)rientation.</Commentary>
  </ClassAssociates>

  <ClassAssociates>
   <SequenceOrderId>253</SequenceOrderId>
   <Dated>2003-07-29T00:00:00.0000000-08:00</Dated>
   <Commentary>Kokuho Rice U.S. #1 Extra Fancy New Crop Net Wt. 20LBS 9.07kg.: Noise Kirkland Signature by Whirlpool Corporation. Model: SS22AEXHW01. Serial No. SK2643921. Manufacture Date: 06-00. Manufactured for Costco Wholesale Corporation by Whirlpool Corporation. Whirlpool Corporation. Benton Harbor, MI 49022. Computer, on, garage noise.</Commentary>
  </ClassAssociates>

  <ClassAssociates>
   <SequenceOrderId>254</SequenceOrderId>
   <Dated>2003-07-29T00:00:00.0000000-08:00</Dated>
   <Commentary>4733 Mallard Common Fremont CA 94560: Go ahead. .NET Framework SDK Version 1.1: 99% complete, error.</Commentary>
  </ClassAssociates>
  
  </TheWord>
</wordOfGod>