<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type='text/xsl' href='TheWord.xslt'?>
<wordOfGod>
 <TheWord>
  <SequenceOrderId>26</SequenceOrderId>
  <Dated>2003-08-05T00:00:00.0000000-08:00</Dated>
  <ScriptureReference>Exodus 16:6, Exodus 16:12, 2 Chronicles 13:5, 2 Chronicles 30:22, Ezekiel 34:30, Joel 2:14, 2 Corinthians 1:14, 2 Peter 1:14</ScriptureReference>
  <ScriptureReferenceURI>http://bible.crosswalk.com/OnlineStudyBible/bible.cgi?new=1&amp;word=Exodus+16%3A6%2C+Exodus+16%3A12%2C+2+Chronicles+13%3A5%2C+2+Chronicles+30%3A22%2C+Ezekiel+34%3A30%2C+Joel+2%3A14%2C+2+Corinthians+1%3A14%2C+2+Peter+1%3A14&amp;section=0&amp;version=nkj&amp;language=en</ScriptureReferenceURI>  
  <Title>How many days does it take to know You, LORD?</Title>
  <Commentary />
  <Keyword />

  <Remember>
   <SequenceOrderId>329</SequenceOrderId>
   <DatedFrom>2003-07-18T00:00:00.0000000-08:00</DatedFrom>
   <DatedUntil>2003-08-05T00:00:00.0000000-08:00</DatedUntil>
   <SignIndex>18</SignIndex>
   <Commentary>There is no one to guide her among all the sons she has brought forth; nor is there any who takes by the hand among all the sons she has brought up" (Isaiah 51:18).</Commentary>
   <Filename>Comforter_-_20030718AlwaysWorking.xml</Filename>
   <ScriptureReference>Isaiah 51:18, Isaiah 63:15, Luke 1:75</ScriptureReference>   
   <ScriptureReferenceURI>http://bible.crosswalk.com/OnlineStudyBible/bible.cgi?new=1&amp;word=Isaiah+51%3A18%2C+Isaiah+63%3A15%2C+Luke+1%3A75&amp;section=0&amp;version=nkj&amp;language=en</ScriptureReferenceURI>   
  </Remember>

  <Remember>
   <SequenceOrderId>330</SequenceOrderId>
   <DatedFrom>2003-07-24T00:00:00.0000000-08:00</DatedFrom>
   <DatedUntil>2003-08-06T00:00:00.0000000-08:00</DatedUntil>
   <SignIndex>13</SignIndex>
   <Commentary>Sulfresh XA Bong Luu Huynh Nhu Tam Suoi Nuoc Nong Khu Trung Diel Mun. Sulfresh 80g. (3 oz.) Nuoi Da Dung Sac. Packed for Anhing Corp LA CA 90031 (213) 221 8003. PT. Primasindo Medikamas Pharmaceuticals.</Commentary>
   <Filename>Comforter_-_20030724ByThisTheWorldWillKnowThatYouAreMyDisciplesIfYouLoveOneAnotherAsIHaveLovedYou.xml</Filename>
   <ScriptureReference>Luke 8:15, Luke 21:19, Romans 5:3-4, Romans 15:4-5, 2 Corinthians 12:12, Colossians 1:11, 1 Thessalonians 1:3, 2 Thessalonians 1:4, 1 Timothy 6:11, 2 Timothy 3:10, Titus 2:2, Revelation 14:12</ScriptureReference>
   <ScriptureReferenceURI>http://bible.crosswalk.com/OnlineStudyBible/bible.cgi?new=1&amp;word=Luke+8%3A15%2C+Luke+21%3A19%2C+Romans+5%3A3-4%2C+Romans+15%3A4-5%2C+2+Corinthians+12%3A12%2C+Colossians+1%3A11%2C+1+Thessalonians+1%3A3%2C+2+Thessalonians+1%3A4%2C+1+Timothy+6%3A11%2C+2+Timothy+3%3A10%2C+Titus+2%3A2%2C+Revelation+14%3A12&amp;section=0&amp;version=nkj&amp;language=en</ScriptureReferenceURI>
  </Remember>

  <!--
  <ScriptureReading>
   <SequenceOrderId>64</SequenceOrderId>
   <ScriptureReference></ScriptureReference>
   <ScriptureReferenceURI></ScriptureReferenceURI>
  </ScriptureReading>
  -->

  <Sign>
   <SequenceOrderId>21</SequenceOrderId>
   <Measure>Day</Measure>
   <SignIndex>13</SignIndex>
   <Commentary>There are 13 days, and this is the 26th TheWord. The Sulfresh XA Bong Luu Huynh Nhu Tam Suoi Nuoc Nong Khu Trung Diel Mun. Sulfresh 80g. (3 oz.) Nuoi Da Dung Sac. Packed for Anhing Corp LA CA 90031 (213) 221 8003. PT. Primasindo Medikamas Pharmaceuticals is in 2 parts.</Commentary>
   <ScriptureReference>Esther 3:12-13, Esther 8:12, Esther 9:1, Esther 9:17-18</ScriptureReference>
   <ScriptureReferenceURI>http://bible.crosswalk.com/OnlineStudyBible/bible.cgi?new=1&amp;word=Esther+3%3A12-13%2C+Esther+8%3A12%2C+Esther+9%3A1%2C+Esther+9%3A17-18&amp;section=0&amp;version=nkj&amp;language=en</ScriptureReferenceURI>
  </Sign>

  <BibleWord>
   <SequenceOrderId>202</SequenceOrderId>
   <Word>Know ... LORD (even)</Word>
   <Commentary>
Moses and Aaron said unto all the children of Israel, At even, then you shall know that the LORD has brought you out from the land of Egypt (Exodus 16:6).
I have heard the murmurings of the children of Israel: speak unto them, saying, At even you shall eat flesh, and in the morning you shall be filled with bread; and you shall know that I am the LORD Your God (Exodus 16:12).
Ought you not to know that the LORD God of Israel gave the kingdom over Israel to David for ever, even to him and to his sons by a covenant of salt? (2 Chronicles 13:5).
Hezekiah spoke comfortably unto all the Levites that taught the good knowledge of the LORD: and they did eat throughout the feast seven days, offering peace offerings, and making confession to the LORD God of their fathers (2 Chronicles 30:22).
This shall they know that I the LORD their God am with them, and that they, even the house of Israel, are My people, said the Lord GOD (Ezekiel 34:30).
Who knows if he will return and repent, and leave a blessing behind him; even a meat offering and a drink offering unto the LORD your God? (Joel 2:14).
As also you have acknowledged us in part, that we are your rejoicing, even as you also are our's in the day of the Lord Jesus (2 Corinthians 1:14).
Knowing that shortly I must put off this my tabernacle, even as our Lord Jesus Christ has showed me (2 Peter 1:14).
   </Commentary>
  </BibleWord>

  <AlphabetSequence>
   <SequenceOrderId>479</SequenceOrderId>
   <Word>How many days does it take to know You, LORD?</Word>
   <AlphabetSequenceIndex>465</AlphabetSequenceIndex>
   <ScriptureReference>Genesis 19:7, Job 29, Isaiah 46, 1 John 5:13</ScriptureReference>
   <ScriptureReferenceURI>http://bible.crosswalk.com/OnlineStudyBible/bible.cgi?new=1&amp;word=Genesis+19%3A7%2C+Job+29%2C+Isaiah+46%2C+1+John+5%3A13&amp;section=0&amp;version=nkj&amp;language=en</ScriptureReferenceURI>  
  </AlphabetSequence>

  <CaseBasedReasoning>
   <SequenceOrderId>1056</SequenceOrderId>
   <Commentary>The intersection of Fremont Blvd and Highway 84: Touch elbow, right. The intersection of Fremont Blvd and Mowry, Washington Mutual across the street: fly below the left eye. Before the intersection of Cherry Street and Moores Avenue, fly on the left cheek. The left computer, Comfort, housekeeping, remove the Comforter_-_20030805IPrayYourGodWillSeeMeNow*.* and Comforter_-_20030805TheWord.sql files, bug, on the front window binder moving towards the left. Comforter_-_200307101700TheWorldWillContinueToLookAtUsInDimLight.xml: Fly, towards the right.</Commentary>
  </CaseBasedReasoning>

  <CaseBasedReasoning>
   <SequenceOrderId>1057</SequenceOrderId>
   <Dated>2003-08-06T00:00:00.0000000-08:00</Dated>
   <Commentary>Wake-up Orientation: Knees bowed, horizontal between 25% and 50%, vertical between 0% and 66.67%. Wake-up Orientation: Center, Knees crossed. Wake-up Orientation: Knees bowed, horizontal between 25% and 33%, vertical between 0% and 66.67%, middle 50%, knees 33%, the right fingers above the left fingers starting from the 4th left finger, the right feets above the left feets starting from the 4th left feet. Eye, right, sore. Record, heart beat, left: The right turn prior to reaching the intersection of Stevenson Blvd and Blacow Road, in front of the Albertsons and beside the Fremont Bank: Truck, black. 17th, 4th row and 4th column, Sulfresh XA Bong Luu Huynh Nhu Tam Suoi Nuoc Nong Khu Trung Diel Mun. Sulfresh 80g. (3 oz.) Nuoi Da Dung Sac. Packed for Anhing Corp LA CA 90031 (213) 221 8003. PT. Primasindo Medikamas Pharmaceuticals. Lake Blvd. Food4Less 39966 Cedar Blvd Newark 94560 CA French Baguettes. Kokuho Rice U.S. #1 Extra Fancy New Crop Net Wt. 20LBS 9.07kg.</Commentary>
  </CaseBasedReasoning>

  <!--
  <Export>
   <SequenceOrderId>24</SequenceOrderId>
   <Commentary></Commentary>
  </Export>
  -->

  <!--
  <Software>
   <SequenceOrderId>243</SequenceOrderId>
   <Commentary></Commentary>
  </Software>
  -->
    
  <ClassAssociates>
   <SequenceOrderId>273</SequenceOrderId>
   <Commentary>The right turn prior to reaching the intersection of Stevenson Blvd and Blacow Road, in front of the Albertsons and beside the Fremont Bank: Truck, black. Highway 880 Stevenson Exit, car music noise, motorcycle screech. Shop: You are looking back. Floppy disk housekeeping on the left computer, Comfort, noise ... open the front door. (C). SQL Query ... There are 18 days between 20030718 and 20030805 (,). AlphabetSequence: How many days (d)eos.</Commentary>
  </ClassAssociates>

  <ClassAssociates>
   <SequenceOrderId>274</SequenceOrderId>
   <Dated>2003-08-06T00:00:00.0000000-08:00</Dated>
   <Commentary>Dog No(i)se. SELECT * FROM CaseBasedReasoning WHERE  ((D)ated (Less than)Greater than = '20030805') ORDER BY SequenceOrderId. Open the front door. SELECT * FROM Remember Noise. (L)uke 8:15. There are 13 days, and this is the 26th TheWord ... CaseBasedReasoning 1057 Garage noise ... 2003-08-0(7)6. Record: 66.67%, left computer, Comfort, noise. Database archive error.</Commentary>
  </ClassAssociates>

  </TheWord>
</wordOfGod>